<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<reply>
	<programs>
		<program>
			<id>43151</id>
			<name>Howrse - US/AU/DE/DK/NO/CZ/SE/FI - Non Incentivized</name>
			<url>www.matomy.com</url>
			<association_status>Approved</association_status>
			<logo>http://network.adsmarket.com/site/StoredImage?cid=1178d507</logo>
			<description><![CDATA[&lt;b&gt;Program Title:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;span style="white-space: pre; "&gt;	&lt;/span&gt;Howrse &lt;b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;span style="white-space:pre"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;Browser game &lt;/b&gt;about the horse back riding world where you can take care of a horse, organize competitions, have your own equestrian center and hire staff to run your center.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;b&gt;Affiliate Benefits:&lt;span style="white-space:pre"&gt;	&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;Pay per registration. Really high conversion rates. Single opt-in.&amp;nbsp;&lt;b&gt;User Flow:&lt;/b&gt;Screen 1: Select pony or horse and gender. Screen 2: Select breed and coat. Screen 3: Enter user&rsquo;s login (username and password), their e-mail, password, date of birth and if relevant their sponsor. End of the registration. &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;b&gt;Typical Demographics:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/b&gt;Female over 13&lt;br&gt;]]></description>
			<restrictions><![CDATA[&lt;b&gt;This program is under budget, please contact your affiliate manager to get more information.&lt;br&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;b&gt;In order to run this offer with Adwords, please contact your account manager.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Traffic only from markets written in the campaign name. No Virtual currency traffic. No Co- Reg traffic.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Valid Conversion Criteria: 3 Steps: 1. Choose a horse or pony (check the box) + Give a name + Choose male or female (Check the box) 2. Choose a breed for the horse (Check the box) and the color (Check the box) 3. Identifier+password+ email address (not verified) +Date of birth+ check the T&amp;amp;C. The pixel fires after the user clicks on the box &ldquo;End Registration&rdquo;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;It is forbidden to use the name or image of Meredith Michaels-Beerbaum in any creatives.&lt;/b&gt;]]></restrictions>
			<tc>
			</tc>
			<categories>Games</categories>
			<mobile_tags>
			</mobile_tags>
			<countries> AU, CZ, DK, FI, DE, NO, SE, US</countries>
			<media_types>Display, Email, GDN, Pops, Social</media_types>
			<languages> eng</languages>
			<tracking_duration>45</tracking_duration>
			<deep_links>0</deep_links>
			<date_created>2011-10-24 13:18:26</date_created>
			<date_updated>2015-01-12 03:40:39</date_updated>
		</program>
		<program>
			<id>44261</id>
			<name>Goodgame Empire - Non Incentivized</name>
			<url>www.matomy.com</url>
			<association_status>Approved</association_status>
			<logo>http://network.adsmarket.com/site/StoredImage?cid=1153830b</logo>
			<description><![CDATA[&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Browser game&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Become the lord of a castle and turn your small fortress
into the capital of the entire kingdom in this exciting online strategy game.
Establish an efficient economic system and assemble a mighty army to defend
your realm and extend your territory. Forge alliances with other players
worldwide to crush your enemies, and become the sole ruler of a mighty empire!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight:bold;"&gt;Target group&lt;/span&gt;: male, between 13 - 35 years&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight:bold;"&gt;Flow:&lt;/span&gt; Single Optin: can create avatar but dont have to, fill in username, email address, password, accept T&amp;amp;Cs&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight:bold;"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;]]></description>
			<restrictions><![CDATA[&lt;span style="font-weight:bold;"&gt;** This program is live under budget, please contact your account manager.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight:bold;"&gt;Publishers who can send sub_id's, please send via DP2, numeric values only.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Traffic allowed according to campaign countryno Co-Registrationno Brand biddingno Virtual Currencyno Bing SEM allowedno Google SEM&amp;nbsp;No Content Network (no GDN or yandex, specifically) or otherPop up/under banners are allowed;&amp;nbsp;Site-unders / pop ups of Landing Page also allowedinterstitial sites are ok; Landing page Integration in Websites or Apps is not allowed; blacklisted sites: Comission Junction (http://www.cj.com/) Affiliate Network&amp;nbsp;Glispa (http://www.glispa.com/) as a traffic source; http://share-links.biz/;http://free-mp3-albums.com; icyfiles.com; freakshare.com; bitshare.com; filecatory.com; xvidstage.com; dimshare.com;http://www.wyspagier.pl; &amp;nbsp;http://www.mary.com;http://www.brincar.pthttp://chulojuegos.comhttp://www.titter.es&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;additional&amp;nbsp;Leukespellen.beIgry.byHrajted.czlege.dkSpilleland.comGladespil.dkTitter.dkFunnygames.co.ukTessagames.co.ukFunnycoloring.comJeuxgratuits.frTitter.frIeuxdroles.frUniversdesjeux.frColoriage.orgWyspagier.plmultumgier.plFlashgierki.plTitter.plJakoloruje.plBrincar.ptTitter.ptDesenhos.ptSkojspel.seJocuri.net1001jocuri.comJoacajocuri.roTitter.roIgriigri.ruIgrytessy.ruHry.netTitter.esIuegoswapos.esChulojuegos.comDiibujos.orgFunspiele.chOyunyolu.netOyunlaradasi.comMary.comGamesclub.comJocjogos.comJogosloucos.com.brJogarlegal.com.brGoodgame.co.inMinigame.com.twMinigame.com.cnWarda.comSpiel.deSpielkarussell.deTessaspiele.deJetzmalen.deTitter.grJatekok.netTitter.huGiocare.itIsoladeigiochi.itUniversodelgioco.itColorare.itSpeeleiland.nlSpelletje.nlTitter.nlNukleuren.nlSpille.noMinespill.comGratisspill.noTRAFFIC RESTRICTIONS:Social (Facebook and other social networks)Illegal Sites*Inappropriate Sites**Third party program resellingPop up of GOODGAMES hosted sitesNo automatic entry services* The Affiliate/Publisher Party agrees to obey all applicable legal requirements in respect of used traffic sources. Displaying GOODGAMES creatives on websites violating or infringing the respectively applicable laws and regulations is not allowed. Additionally, GOODGAMES may send Advertising Party a &lsquo;blacklist&rsquo; containing exemplary websites.&lt;br&gt;** Displaying GOODGAMES creatives on websites which include, refer to or link directly or indirectly to content unsuitable for persons under 18 year olds including online gambling with real money, nudity and pornography, cigarettes and alcohol and drugs is not allowed.&lt;br&gt;Valid Conversion Criteria:Flow: fill in username, email address, password, accept T&amp;amp;CsAPPROVAL OF CREATIVES: Only creatives provided by GOODGAMES may be utilized by the Affiliate/Publisher Party. Creatives created by the Affiliate/Publisher Party, need to be pre-approved in writing (email) by GOODGAMES. In particular use of ads with sound is prohibited under this agreement.&lt;br&gt;Search (Bing) restrictions:Bidding on the brand "Goodgame Studios" and/or any combination of this as well as typing mistakes are not allowed. The same applies for all games of Goodgame Studios.List of negative Keywords:goodgame Empire,goodgame Mafia, goodgame Cafe, goodgame Farm Fever, goodgame Farmer, goodgame Poker, goodgame Fashion, goodgame DiscoJump Jupiter, goodgame Jump JupiterMust book these keywords as negatives (excluding keywords and if possible with the option 'broad') so they won't be added automatically by the search network.FRAUD detection: &amp;nbsp;fraud will be evaluated according to several parameters:&bull;&lt;span style="white-space: pre;"&gt;	&lt;/span&gt;player activity (mostly none activity at all)&bull;&lt;span style="white-space:pre"&gt;	&lt;/span&gt;registration name&amp;nbsp;&bull;&lt;span style="white-space:pre"&gt;	&lt;/span&gt;mail address&bull;&lt;span style="white-space:pre"&gt;	&lt;/span&gt;combination of mail address and registration name&bull;&lt;span style="white-space:pre"&gt;	&lt;/span&gt;time stamp&amp;nbsp;&bull;&lt;span style="white-space:pre"&gt;	&lt;/span&gt;ip address &lt;br&gt;Do NOT use iFrame placements&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;wildtangent.com&lt;br&gt;relink.us&lt;br&gt;
share-links.biz&lt;br&gt;
linkcrypt.ws&lt;br&gt;
linksave.in&lt;br&gt;
ncrypt.in&lt;br&gt;
boerse.bz&lt;br&gt;
serienjunkies.org&lt;br&gt;
mygully.com&lt;br&gt;
movie-blog.org&lt;br&gt;
ddl-warez.in&lt;br&gt;
c1neon.com&lt;br&gt;
hd-area.org&lt;br&gt;
mov-world.net&lt;br&gt;
leecher.to&lt;br&gt;
1load.net&lt;br&gt;
hd-world.org&lt;br&gt;
speedlounge.in&lt;br&gt;
moviebox.to&lt;br&gt;
cinetopia.ws&lt;br&gt;
dnblog.in&lt;br&gt;
funxd.in&lt;br&gt;
moviekk.net&lt;br&gt;
goldesel.to&lt;br&gt;
movie4k.to&lt;br&gt;
kinox.to&lt;br&gt;
movie-stream.to&lt;br&gt;
cine24.tv&lt;br&gt;
loads7.com&lt;br&gt;
online-moviez.com&lt;br&gt;
filme2k.netgirlsgogames.comgamesgames.comagame.comzibbo.coma10.comgirlsgogames.co.ukagame.comgames.co.ukjuegosdechicas.comzapjuegos.comjuegos.comgirlsgogames.ruflashgames.ruourgames.ruojogos.ptgirlsgogames.plgry.plgirlsgogames.nlspel.nlspelletjes.nlItalygirlsgogames.itgiochi.itgioco.itgirlsgogames.despielen.comjetztspielen.degirlsgogames.com.troyunoyna.comgirlsgogames.frjeu.frjeux.frgirlsgogames.sespel.sespela.segirlsgogames.comagame.comgamesgames.comjuegosdechicas.comzapjuegos.comjuegos.comjuegosdechicas.comzapjuegos.comjuegos.comgirlsgogames.com.brojogos.com.brjuegosdechicas.comzapjuegos.comjuegos.comgirlsgogames.com.tr&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;]]></restrictions>
			<tc>
			</tc>
			<categories>Games</categories>
			<mobile_tags>
			</mobile_tags>
			<countries> AR, AU, AT, BE, BR, BG, CA, CZ, DK, EG, FI, FR, DE, GR, HU, IN, IT, JP, KR, MX, NL, NO, PL, PT, RO, RU, SA, SK, ES, SE, CH, AE, GB, US</countries>
			<media_types>Display</media_types>
			<languages> ger</languages>
			<tracking_duration>30</tracking_duration>
			<deep_links>0</deep_links>
			<date_created>2011-11-07 04:14:50</date_created>
			<date_updated>2015-01-12 03:41:56</date_updated>
		</program>
		<program>
			<id>44541</id>
			<name>Drakensang - Int'l - Non Incent</name>
			<url>http://www.drakensang.com/</url>
			<association_status>Approved</association_status>
			<logo>http://network.adsmarket.com/site/StoredImage?cid=38db4dc1</logo>
			<description><![CDATA[&lt;span style="font-weight:bold;"&gt;Browsergame&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/span&gt;DrakensangOnline
 is the first browser-based action online RPG in the famous Drakensang 
saga that stands above the rest thanks to its visually-stunning graphics
 and detailed game world. In the struggle to save humanity from the dark
 forces of the Ander world, players are challenged to master numerous 
quests and test their mettle against fierce competition in different 
arenas.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight:bold;"&gt;Target: &lt;/span&gt;Gaming Channel, Males in the 18-55 demo&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight:bold;"&gt;Flow:&lt;/span&gt; Single Optin, enter username, password, email address, enter captcha Code&lt;br&gt;]]></description>
			<restrictions><![CDATA[&lt;p style="direction: ltr; unicode-bidi: embed;"&gt;&lt;b&gt;This
program is under budget, please contact you&lt;span style="color:#1F497D"&gt;r&lt;/span&gt;
affiliate manager to get more information. Please consider a cap of max 70 leads/day/pub till further feedback.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="direction: ltr; unicode-bidi: embed;"&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="direction: ltr; unicode-bidi: embed;"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11.0pt;font-family:&amp;quot;Calibri&amp;quot;,sans-serif;
mso-fareast-font-family:Calibri;mso-fareast-theme-font:minor-latin;mso-bidi-font-family:
&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;;color:#1F497D;mso-ansi-language:EN-US;mso-fareast-language:
EN-US;mso-bidi-language:AR-SA"&gt;Be aware &ndash; advertiser will deny fraudulent leads
without providing detailed proof per lead. Please take this under consideration
when running the program.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;Blacklisted websites:&lt;br&gt;&lt;p style="margin-top: 0in; margin-right: 0in; margin-bottom: 0pt; margin-left: 0in; "&gt;&lt;span style="background-color: rgb(255, 255, 255); color: rgb(102, 102, 102); "&gt;Kinox.to&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="margin-top: 0in; margin-right: 0in; margin-bottom: 0pt; margin-left: 0in; "&gt;&lt;span style="background-color: rgb(255, 255, 255); color: rgb(102, 102, 102); "&gt;Kino.to&lt;/span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="margin-top: 0in; margin-right: 0in; margin-bottom: 0pt; margin-left: 0in; "&gt;freakshare.com&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="margin-top: 0in; margin-right: 0in; margin-bottom: 0pt; margin-left: 0in; "&gt;icyfiles.com&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="margin-top: 0in; margin-right: 0in; margin-bottom: 0pt; margin-left: 0in; "&gt;bitshare.com&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="margin-top: 0in; margin-right: 0in; margin-bottom: 0pt; margin-left: 0in; "&gt;filefactory.com&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="margin-top: 0in; margin-right: 0in; margin-bottom: 0pt; margin-left: 0in; "&gt;xvidstage.com&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="margin-top: 0in; margin-right: 0in; margin-bottom: 0pt; margin-left: 0in; "&gt;dimshare.com&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;Websites that offer downloadable films which can be considered harmful to youth (films indexed by the Federal Department for Media Harmful to Young Person [BPjM] an/or those defined as very harmful to youth due to content violating &sect;&sect; 130, 130a, 131, 184 of the German Penal Code [StGB] in accordance with &sect; 15 para. 2 of the Law for the Protection of Children and Young People [JuSchG] and do not have protective measures in place to prevent minors from accessing them). This applies particularly, but not exclusively, to the following websites:&lt;br&gt;-&lt;span style="white-space:pre"&gt;	&lt;/span&gt;linkcrypt.ws-&lt;span style="white-space:pre"&gt;	&lt;/span&gt;linksave.in-&lt;span style="white-space:pre"&gt;	&lt;/span&gt;share-links.biz-&lt;span style="white-space:pre"&gt;	&lt;/span&gt;relink.us&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;]]></restrictions>
			<tc>
			</tc>
			<categories>Games</categories>
			<mobile_tags>
			</mobile_tags>
			<countries> AF, AX, AL, AS, AD, AO, AI, A1, AQ, AG, AR, AM, AW, AP, AU, AT, AZ, BS, BD, BB, BY, BE, BZ, BJ, BM, BT, BO, BQ, BA, BW, BV, BR, IO, BN, BG, BF, BI, KH, CM, CA, CV, KY, CF, TD, CL, CX, CC, CO, KM, CG, CD, CK, CR, CI, HR, CU, CW, CY, CZ, DK, DJ, DM, DO, TP, EC, SV, GQ, ER, EE, ET, EU, FK, FO, FJ, FI, FR, GF, PF, TF, GA, GM, GE, DE, GH, GI, GR, GL, GD, GP, GU, GT, GG, GN, GW, GY, HT, HM, HN, HK, HU, IS, ID, IE, IM, IT, JM, JE, KZ, KE, KI, KG, LA, LV, LS, LR, LI, LT, LU, MO, MK, MG, MW, MV, ML, MT, MH, MQ, MR, MU, YT, MX, FM, MD, MC, MN, ME, MS, MZ, MM, NA, NR, NP, NL, AN, NC, NZ, NI, NE, NG, NU, NF, MP, NO, PK, PW, PA, PG, PY, PE, PN, PL, PT, PR, RE, RO, RU, RW, SH, KN, LC, MF, PM, VC, WS, SM, ST, A2, SN, RS, SC, SL, SK, SI, SB, SO, ZA, GS, ES, LK, SD, SR, SJ, SZ, SE, CH, TJ, TZ, TL, TG, TK, TO, TT, TR, TM, TC, TV, UG, UA, GB, US, UM, UY, UZ, VU, VA, VE, VN, VG, VI, WF, EH, ZM, ZW</countries>
			<media_types>Display, Email, Social</media_types>
			<languages>
			</languages>
			<tracking_duration>30</tracking_duration>
			<deep_links>0</deep_links>
			<date_created>2011-11-10 11:45:07</date_created>
			<date_updated>2015-03-05 04:40:00</date_updated>
		</program>
		<program>
			<id>51821</id>
			<name>Video Download Converter - US - (HJxdm035)</name>
			<url>www.matomy.com</url>
			<association_status>Approved</association_status>
			<description><![CDATA[Easily convert videos into MP3s! - Download videos from YouTube, Vimeo, MTV.com, and more!&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mindspark is the oldest provider of fun, free downloads on the web! Your users will love the silly smileys at SmileyCentral, screensavers with Popular AS, and glitter, nature, and other whimsical desktop wallpaper designs. We continuously update our products and sites to give Publishers lots of fresh, new and fun offers that are sure to bring a boost of color to your visitor's computer! &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;User Flow: User gets to the landing page, downloads the application and installs on his/her computer.]]></description>
			<restrictions><![CDATA[this program is capped, please contact your dedicated account manager in order to be associated to this program.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;b&gt;US traffic only.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Publishers that are interested in running any IAC 
program must sign this addendum first: 
http://docs.matomy.com/1/Advertisers/Forms/IAC-publisher-addendum.pdf&lt;br&gt;Link to complete IAC Guidelines: http://docs.matomy.com/1/Publishers/IAC-guidlines.pdf.&lt;br&gt;Association upon Matomy account manager approval only.&lt;br&gt;DISPLAY
 ONLY. No Incentivized, No content locking, no VC. No distribution 
through adware or spyware. No distribution on sites for children under 
13. No distribution on sites owned, operated or managed by Mindspark or 
any of it's affiliated companies.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;Valid lead criteria: user downloads and installs the product. Pixel fires upon successful installation.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;Browsers: IE and FF only. This application is not compliant with other browsers.&lt;br&gt;All
 creatives must be approved by the advertiser. The usage of 
Creatives/texts (banners, e-mail, text ads etc) that were not provided 
by the advertiser, will only be allowed upon the advertiser's approval. 
Please contact the relevant Adsmarket representative/account manager if 
you wish to approve the usage of such creatives. All creatives (even if 
previously approved by the advertiser) must include the relevant IAC 
product's logo. The borders (frames) of all banners must be visible to 
the viewer, and cannot blend into the background of the site where it is
 displayed. No mention of Hulu is permitted. No duplicate IPs. &amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Pubs
 are NOT allowed to mention any reference of "Elf Yourself" in any of 
client's ads, ad copy or landing pages for any of the products as this 
is a trademarked name.&lt;br&gt;Mindspark offers are not to be advertised via PageRage or any of it's affiliates&lt;br&gt;Advertising is not allowed on firstrowsports.eu. Please see guidelines for full list of sites to blacklist.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;Ads cannot be placed so that they are covering/on top of media players. &amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;Ads are not allowed to reference any text/content offering special access to premium content/materials, or to live broadcast TV.&lt;br&gt;Facebook traffic of any kind is not allowed. A publisher 
who will use Facebook to promote this program will not be compensated 
for generated commissions and will risk suspension from Matomy Market&lt;br&gt;&lt;p style="margin: 10px 0px 0px; padding: 0px; color: rgb(51, 51, 51); font-family: Arial, sans-serif; font-size: 14px; line-height: 20px; background-color: rgb(255, 255, 255);"&gt;GDN is allowed as long as creatives/texts are provided by/approved by the advertiser.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="margin: 10px 0px 0px; padding: 0px; color: rgb(51, 51, 51); font-family: Arial, sans-serif; font-size: 14px; line-height: 20px; background-color: rgb(255, 255, 255);"&gt;No torrents or peer-to-peer traffic.&lt;/p&gt;]]></restrictions>
			<tc>
			</tc>
			<categories>Downloads</categories>
			<mobile_tags>
			</mobile_tags>
			<countries> US</countries>
			<media_types>Display, Email, Pops, GDN</media_types>
			<languages> eng</languages>
			<tracking_duration>45</tracking_duration>
			<deep_links>0</deep_links>
			<date_created>2012-03-01 11:47:20</date_created>
			<date_updated>2014-11-03 06:06:24</date_updated>
		</program>
		<program>
			<id>52321</id>
			<name>Stronghold kingdoms US- Non incentivised</name>
			<url>www.matomy.com</url>
			<association_status>Approved</association_status>
			<logo>http://network.adsmarket.com/site/StoredImage?cid=1657d0b9</logo>
			<description><![CDATA[&lt;span style="font-weight: bold;"&gt;Download game&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;span style="text-decoration: underline; font-weight: bold;"&gt;Offer Review:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;
Stronghold Kingdoms is the medieval online castle game. Join hundreds of
 thousands of players in a rich world of Lords, Ladies, Bumpkins and 
Barons as you build your village, research new technology and strive to 
be the greatest in the land. Construct mighty castles to defend your 
lands against insolent intruders, develop your economy and trade your 
way to victory, lead your fellow noblemen to war and control of the 
Kingdom. Build, besiege, pillage, farm, explore, research, vote, trade 
and banquet your way to the throne!&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;span style="text-decoration: underline; font-weight: bold;"&gt;User Flow:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;Email, password x2, SOI&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;span style="text-decoration: underline; font-weight: bold;"&gt;Typical Demographics:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;span style="text-decoration: underline;"&gt;High-Rollers:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;
Age: 35-50&lt;br&gt;
Gender: Predominantly Male&lt;br&gt;
&lt;span style="text-decoration: underline;"&gt;Overall Demographics:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;
Age: 13-55&lt;br&gt;
Gender: 91% Male / 9% Female&lt;span&gt;	&lt;/span&gt;]]></description>
			<restrictions><![CDATA[&lt;b&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/b&gt;]]></restrictions>
			<tc>
			</tc>
			<categories>Games</categories>
			<mobile_tags>
			</mobile_tags>
			<countries> US</countries>
			<media_types>Display, Social</media_types>
			<languages>
			</languages>
			<tracking_duration>30</tracking_duration>
			<deep_links>0</deep_links>
			<date_created>2012-03-08 06:16:16</date_created>
			<date_updated>2015-01-12 04:31:01</date_updated>
		</program>
		<program>
			<id>63051</id>
			<name>Radiorage - US (ZXxdm211) - Display Only</name>
			<url>www.matomy.com</url>
			<association_status>Approved</association_status>
			<logo>http://network.adsmarket.com/site/StoredImage?cid=2940e6a7</logo>
			<description><![CDATA[Radio rage allows users to play the latest music right from their browser by streaming internet and local radio.&amp;nbsp;Also provides industry news and song recommendations in order to keep listeners up to date and help them to explore different types of music.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;DISPLAY ONLY.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;Valid lead criteria: user downloads and installs the product. Pixel fires upon successful installation.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;&lt;b&gt;*New publishers must cap traffic at $150/day until receiving advertiser feedback that they can increase.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/b&gt;]]></description>
			<restrictions><![CDATA[Publishers that are interested in running any IAC program must sign this addendum first: http://docs.matomy.com/1/Advertisers/Forms/IAC-publisher-addendum.pdf&lt;br&gt;Link to complete IAC Guidelines: http://docs.matomy.com/1/Publishers/IAC-guidlines.pdf.&lt;br&gt;Association upon Matomy account manager approval only.&lt;br&gt;DISPLAY ONLY. No Incentivized, No content locking, no VC. No distribution through adware or spyware. No distribution on sites for children under 13. No distribution on sites owned, operated or managed by Mindspark or any of it's affiliated companies.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;Valid lead criteria: user downloads and installs the product. Pixel fires upon successful installation.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;Browsers: IE and FF only. This application is not compliant with other browsers.&lt;br&gt;US traffic only.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;All creatives must be approved by the advertiser. The usage of Creatives/texts (banners, e-mail, text ads etc) that were not provided by the advertiser, will only be allowed upon the advertiser's approval. Please contact the relevant Adsmarket representative/account manager if you wish to approve the usage of such creatives. All creatives (even if previously approved by the advertiser) must include the relevant IAC product's logo. The borders (frames) of all banners must be visible to the viewer, and cannot blend into the background of the site where it is displayed. No mention of Hulu is permitted. No duplicate IPs. &amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Pubs are NOT allowed to mention any reference of "Elf Yourself" in any of client's ads, ad copy or landing pages for any of the products as this is a trademarked name.&lt;br&gt;Mindspark offers are not to be advertised via PageRage or any of it's affiliates&lt;br&gt;Advertising is not allowed on firstrowsports.eu. Please see guidelines for full list of sites to blacklist.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;Ads cannot be placed so that they are covering/on top of media players. &amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;Ads are not allowed to reference any text/content offering special access to premium content/materials, or to live broadcast TV.&lt;br&gt;No GDN. No SEM. Facebook traffic of any kind is not allowed. A publisher who will use Facebook to promote this program will not be compensated for generated commissions and will risk suspension from Matomy Market&lt;br&gt;&lt;p style="margin: 10px 0px 0px; padding: 0px; color: rgb(51, 51, 51); font-family: Arial, sans-serif; font-size: 14px; line-height: 20px; background-color: rgb(255, 255, 255);"&gt;GDN is allowed as long as creatives/texts are provided by/approved by the advertiser.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="margin: 10px 0px 0px; padding: 0px; color: rgb(51, 51, 51); font-family: Arial, sans-serif; font-size: 14px; line-height: 20px; background-color: rgb(255, 255, 255);"&gt;No torrents or peer-to-peer traffic.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;]]></restrictions>
			<tc>
			</tc>
			<categories>Downloads</categories>
			<mobile_tags>
			</mobile_tags>
			<countries> US</countries>
			<media_types>Display, Email, Pops, GDN</media_types>
			<languages> eng</languages>
			<tracking_duration>45</tracking_duration>
			<deep_links>0</deep_links>
			<date_created>2012-07-01 07:36:46</date_created>
			<date_updated>2014-11-03 06:08:52</date_updated>
		</program>
		<program>
			<id>71141</id>
			<name>Anastasia Date - Intl' - Non Incentivized</name>
			<url>www.matomy.com</url>
			<association_status>Approved</association_status>
			<logo>http://network.adsmarket.com/site/StoredImage?cid=1d385b8d</logo>
			<description><![CDATA[&lt;span style="font-weight: bold; text-decoration: underline;"&gt;Offer Review:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;AnastasiaDate owns and operates one of the largest international dating networks in the world.&lt;br&gt;AnastasiaDate has a Family Safe status.&lt;br&gt;A publisher will get a commission for the 1st page submit lead.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: bold; text-decoration: underline;"&gt;User Flow:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;The conversion takes place after a client fill in the registration form. It is first page submit with no verification via email.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: bold; text-decoration: underline;"&gt;Typical Demographics:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;All the countries that are in the targeting. Male 30-60&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;]]></description>
			<restrictions><![CDATA[&lt;b&gt;New publishers have a &amp;nbsp;cap of 100 leads daily until receiving the advertiser's approval to continue sending traffic.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;b&gt;New publishers running Tier 1 countries should stick to 50 leads daily cap.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;b&gt;In order to run this offer with Adwords, please contact your account manager.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;No Adult site allowed&lt;br&gt;No Viral traffic&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;No rebrokeing&lt;br&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;u&gt;Keyword Restrictions:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;span style="text-indent: -18pt;"&gt;1)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="text-indent: -18pt; font-size: 7pt; font-family: 'Times New Roman';"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="text-indent: -18pt;"&gt;Affiliates are not permitted to advertise in search advertising
using keywords specific to AnastasiaDate, RussianBrides, AsianBeauties,
AsianDate, AmoLatina, ArabianDate,TripTogether (e.g. AnastasiaDate, Anastasia
Romance, Anastasia International, AnastasiaWeb, Anastasia, RussianBrides, AsianBeauties,
AmoLatina, ArabianDate, TripTogether etc.) and variations in terms of
punctuation, spelling, the addition of words and/or the addition the addition
of top-level domains (e.g. AnastasiaDate.com&hellip;).&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="text-indent: -18pt;"&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="text-indent: -18pt;"&gt;2)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="text-indent: -18pt; font-size: 7pt; font-family: 'Times New Roman';"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="text-indent: -18pt;"&gt;Affiliates are not allowed to use exact matches or any
variations of Dream-marriage.com, GlobalLadies.com, CharmingDate.com, ChnLove.com,
Cupid.com and other dating sites.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="text-indent: -18pt;"&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="text-indent: -18pt;"&gt;3)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="text-indent: -18pt; font-size: 7pt; font-family: 'Times New Roman';"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="text-indent: -18pt;"&gt;Affiliates are not permitted to use the following
words as metatags, keywords, hidden text, texts for advertising materials or
other terms: &ldquo;foreign affair&rdquo;, &ldquo;loveme&rdquo;, &ldquo;foreignladies.com&rdquo; and permutations
of these words and phrases; and the exact phrases &ldquo;foreignladies.com&rdquo;,
&ldquo;foreignwomen.com&rdquo; and &ldquo;asiansingles.com.&rdquo;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="text-indent: -18pt;"&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="text-indent: -18pt;"&gt;4)&lt;span style="font-size: 9px;"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="text-indent: -18pt;"&gt;Affiliates are strictly prohibited to use the following
words as metatags, keywords, hidden text, texts for advertising materials or
other terms: &ldquo;Hot Russian Brides&rdquo;, &ldquo;HotRussianBrides.com&rdquo;, &ldquo;Russian Love
Match&rdquo;, &ldquo;RussianLoveMatch.com&rdquo; and variations in terms of punctuation,
spelling, the addition of words and/or the addition the addition of top-level
domains. (e.g. Hotrussianbrides.com, etc.)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p style="margin: 0cm 0cm 0.0001pt 36pt; text-indent: -18pt;"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;]]></restrictions>
			<tc>
			</tc>
			<categories>Dating</categories>
			<mobile_tags>
			</mobile_tags>
			<countries> AU, BE, CA, DK, FR, DE, GR, NL, NZ, NO, ZA, SZ, SE, GB, US</countries>
			<media_types>Display, Email, Mobile Display, Pops, Search</media_types>
			<languages> eng</languages>
			<tracking_duration>45</tracking_duration>
			<deep_links>0</deep_links>
			<date_created>2012-10-04 09:34:24</date_created>
			<date_updated>2014-11-21 12:58:41</date_updated>
		</program>
		<program>
			<id>85731</id>
			<name>Empire: Four Kingdoms - iOS int'l - non incent</name>
			<url>https://itunes.apple.com/de/app/empire-four-kingdoms/id585661281?mt=8</url>
			<association_status>Approved</association_status>
			<logo>http://network.adsmarket.com/site/StoredImage?cid=392a0033</logo>
			<description><![CDATA[*Talk to your Matomy account manager about running this program!*Make ready for battle! Construct fortresses that last for eternity, conquer outposts and establish a flourishing economy. Send out your armies to reduce the castles of enemy players to rubble. Build your mighty empire and compete with thousands of other players. Play now in the huge and visually unique world of Empire: Four Kingdoms!&amp;nbsp;]]></description>
			<restrictions><![CDATA[**This program is under budget. Please contact your Matomy Accout Manager if you are interested in running this program**&lt;br&gt;&lt;b&gt;PLEASE NOTE: Publishers must pass IDFA in all campaigns!&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;valid lead criteria: install app for first time, and open application for first time.iOS Version 6.0, ipad 2+, iphone 4+, &amp;nbsp;and higher; no ipod/ipod touch trafficWIFI/3G;TRAFFIC RESTRICTIONS:a. SEM (Search and Content Networks)b. Co-regse. Virtual Currency / Super &amp;nbsp;Rewards f.. &amp;nbsp;Illegal Sites*h. &amp;nbsp;Inappropriate Sites**&lt;span style="white-space:pre"&gt;	&lt;/span&gt;i. &amp;nbsp;Third party program resellingj. &amp;nbsp;Blacklisted Sites **** The Affiliate/Publisher Party agrees to use commercially reasonable efforts to obey all applicable legal requirements in respect of used traffic sources. Displaying GOODGAMES creatives on websites violating or infringing the respectively applicable laws and regulations is not allowed. Additionally, GOODGAMES may send Advertising Party a &lsquo;blacklist&rsquo; containing exemplary websites.&lt;span style="white-space:pre"&gt;	&lt;/span&gt;** Affiliate/Publisher Party will use commercially reasonable efforts to ensure that GOODGAMES creatives are not displayed on websites which include, refer to or link directly or indirectly to content unsuitable for persons under 18 year olds including online gambling with real money, nudity and pornography, cigarettes and alcohol and drugs is not allowed.Affiliate/Publisher Party will use commercially reasonable efforts to ensure that GOODGAMES creatives are not displayed on websites which include any material, which is deceptive, misleading, offensive, threatening, vulgar, liable to incite racial hatred, discriminatory, menacing or which is racially or ethnically or otherwise objectionable is not allowed.*** Blacklisted Sites (Mobile Sites according to the following Web pages):Icyfiles.com Freakshare.com Bitshare.com Filecatory.com Xvidstage.com Dimshare.comShare-Links.bizFree-mp3-albums.comLeukespellen.beIgry.by&lt;span style="white-space:pre"&gt;	&lt;/span&gt;Hrajted.czlege.dkSpilleland.comGladespil.dkTitter.dkFunnygames.co.ukTessagames.co.ukFunnycoloring.comJeuxgratuits.frTitter.frIeuxdroles.frUniversdesjeux.frColoriage.orgWyspagier.plmultumgier.plFlashgierki.plTitter.plJakoloruje.plBrincar.ptTitter.pt&lt;span style="white-space:pre"&gt;	&lt;/span&gt;Desenhos.ptSkojspel.seJocuri.net1001jocuri.comJoacajocuri.roTitter.roIgriigri.ruIgrytessy.ruHry.netTitter.esIuegoswapos.esChulojuegos.comDiibujos.orgFunspiele.chOyunyolu.netOyunlaradasi.comMary.comGamesclub.comJocjogos.comJogosloucos.com.brJogarlegal.com.brGoodgame.co.in&lt;span style="white-space:pre"&gt;	&lt;/span&gt;Minigame.com.tw Minigame.com.cnWarda.comSpiel.deSpielkarussell.de Tessaspiele.deJetzmalen.deTitter.grJatekok.netTitter.huGiocare.itIsoladeigiochi.itUniversodelgioco.itColorare.itSpeeleiland.nlSpelletje.nlTitter.nlNukleuren.nlSpille.noMinespill.comGratisspill.no,&amp;nbsp;www.applifier.com&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&lt;b&gt;Android OS Android Phone and Tablet:&lt;/b&gt;o&lt;span style="white-space:pre"&gt;	&lt;/span&gt;Android OS Version 4.0 and highero&lt;span style="white-space:pre"&gt;	&lt;/span&gt;Device: excluding Galaxy Young and Kindle (Fire HD)o&lt;span style="white-space:pre"&gt;	&lt;/span&gt;WIFI/3Go&lt;span style="white-space:pre"&gt;	&lt;/span&gt;Non-incentivized traffic]]></restrictions>
			<tc>
			</tc>
			<categories>Mobile Apps,Games</categories>
			<mobile_tags>iOS, iPhone, iPad</mobile_tags>
			<countries> AR, AU, AT, BY, BO, BR, CA, CL, CN, CO, DO, EC, SV, FR, DE, GT, HN, HK, IT, JP, KZ, KR, KG, MO, MX, NL, NI, PA, PY, PE, PL, RU, ES, CH, TW, TR, UA, GB, US, UY, VE</countries>
			<media_types>Display, In App, Mobile Display, Pops</media_types>
			<languages> eng, fre, ger, pol</languages>
			<tracking_duration>45</tracking_duration>
			<deep_links>0</deep_links>
			<date_created>2013-03-24 06:27:39</date_created>
			<date_updated>2014-09-19 04:26:47</date_updated>
		</program>
		<program>
			<id>91391</id>
			<name>Genieo for MAC - Intl'  - Non Incentivized</name>
			<url>www.matomy.com</url>
			<association_status>Approved</association_status>
			<logo>http://network.adsmarket.com/site/StoredImage?cid=256e761b</logo>
			<description><![CDATA[this is an international link program, one link for all geo's, please see valid geo's below:&lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;browsers allowed: FF and Chrome only.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Offer Review: &lt;br&gt;Genieo is the creator of the ultimate recommendation engine which automatically updates its content, reflecting the changing personal interests and needs of each individual. &lt;br&gt;Making users lives easier and more productive.this offer is focused on MAC users around the world.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Affiliate Benefits: &lt;br&gt;Product with a user value that converts well on MAC&lt;br&gt;User Flow: &lt;br&gt;User clicks to download, runs, and installs product completely.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Typical Demographics: &lt;br&gt;USA, MAC users.&lt;br&gt;]]></description>
			<restrictions><![CDATA[this is an international link program, one link for all geo's, please see valid geo's below:&lt;br&gt;Traffic From geo's mentioned below only&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Browsers allowed: FF and Chrome only&lt;br&gt;it is not allowed to run this offer on torrent sites of any kind. &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;PUB PAYOUTS for&amp;nbsp;mac users only :&lt;br&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11.0pt;font-family:&amp;quot;Segoe UI Symbol&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;sans-serif&amp;quot;;
mso-fareast-font-family:Calibri;mso-fareast-theme-font:minor-latin;mso-bidi-font-family:
&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;;mso-ansi-language:EN-US;mso-fareast-language:EN-US;
mso-bidi-language:HE"&gt;http://www.tsxnrey.com/i/526871/91391%20-%20genieo%20-%20rates.pdf&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 14.4444446563721px;"&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;Valid Conversion Criteria:&lt;br&gt;CPI Conversion will fire upon successful arrival to the Thank You Page, regardless of any bundles accepted through the installer flow.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Creative Guidelines:&lt;br&gt;Publishers can use their own creatives&lt;br&gt;Traffic From AU/CA/US/UK/IE/NZ OnlyValid Conversion Criteria:&lt;br&gt;CPI Conversion will fire upon successful arrival to the Thank You Page, regardless of any bundles accepted through the installer flow.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Creative Guidelines:&lt;br&gt;Publishers can use their own creatives however, these generic banners cannot refrences products other than genieo and must include genieo logo. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;For example:&lt;br&gt;Download FLV\VLC now / you are missing a plugin &ndash; is not approved&lt;br&gt;but&lt;br&gt;Download now (not referring to genieo but not to anything else either)&ndash; is approved only with genieo logo added at bottom.&lt;br&gt;]]></restrictions>
			<tc>
			</tc>
			<categories>Downloads</categories>
			<mobile_tags>
			</mobile_tags>
			<countries> AU, AT, BE, CA, DK, FI, FR, DE, IS, IE, IT, JP, LU, NL, AN, NZ, NO, PT, ES, SE, CH, GB, US</countries>
			<media_types>Display, GDN, Pops, Search</media_types>
			<languages>
			</languages>
			<tracking_duration>45</tracking_duration>
			<deep_links>0</deep_links>
			<date_created>2013-06-11 07:29:01</date_created>
			<date_updated>2015-02-10 08:59:24</date_updated>
		</program>
		<program>
			<id>98761</id>
			<name>Empire: Four Kingdoms - Android - Int'l - non incent</name>
			<url>www.matomy.com</url>
			<association_status>Approved</association_status>
			<logo>http://network.adsmarket.com/site/StoredImage?cid=392b9f97</logo>
			<description><![CDATA[Make ready for battle! Construct fortresses that last for eternity, 
conquer outposts and establish a flourishing economy. Send out your 
armies to reduce the castles of enemy players to rubble. Build your 
mighty empire and compete with thousands of other players. Play now in 
the huge and visually unique world of Empire: Four Kingdoms! &lt;br&gt;]]></description>
			<restrictions><![CDATA["This offer is running under budget. Please contact your AM if you wish to run it. Publisher who will not obey this guideline is in risk of denying his leads&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;b&gt;NOTE: Publisher MUST deliver Google Ad ID with all conversions in order for the tracking to work&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;b&gt;&amp;nbsp;pass Google Ad ID at &amp;amp;google_aid=[GAID]&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;valid lead criteria: install app for first time, and open application for first time.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Please note: This program is subject to the Google Play Developer Program Policies, which can be accessed at https://play.google.com/about/developer-content-policy.html&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Device carrier: WIFI/3G&lt;br&gt;Device: Android OS 4.0 and higher excluding Galaxy Young and Kindle (Fire HD)&lt;br&gt;NO TABLETS IN FR &amp;amp; US&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;TRAFFIC RESTRICTIONS:a. SEM (Search and Content 
Networks)b. Co-regse. Virtual Currency / Super &amp;nbsp;Rewardsf. &amp;nbsp;Incentivized 
Traffic (only on explicit permission via IO)g. &amp;nbsp;Illegal Sites*h. 
&amp;nbsp;Inappropriate Sites**&lt;span&gt;	&lt;/span&gt;i. &amp;nbsp;Third 
party program resellingj. &amp;nbsp;Blacklisted Sites **** The 
Affiliate/Publisher Party agrees to use commercially reasonable efforts 
to obey all applicable legal requirements in respect of used traffic 
sources. Displaying GOODGAMES creatives on websites violating or 
infringing the respectively applicable laws and regulations is not 
allowed. Additionally, GOODGAMES may send Advertising Party a 
&lsquo;blacklist&rsquo; containing exemplary websites.&lt;span&gt;	&lt;/span&gt;**
 Affiliate/Publisher Party will use commercially reasonable efforts to 
ensure that GOODGAMES creatives are not displayed on websites which 
include, refer to or link directly or indirectly to content unsuitable 
for persons under 18 year olds including online gambling with real 
money, nudity and pornography, cigarettes and alcohol and drugs is not 
allowed.Affiliate/Publisher Party will use commercially reasonable 
efforts to ensure that GOODGAMES creatives are not displayed on websites
 which include any material, which is deceptive, misleading, offensive, 
threatening, vulgar, liable to incite racial hatred, discriminatory, 
menacing or which is racially or ethnically or otherwise objectionable 
is not allowed.*** Blacklisted Sites (Mobile Sites according to the 
following Web pages):Icyfiles.com Freakshare.com Bitshare.com 
Filecatory.com Xvidstage.com 
Dimshare.comShare-Links.bizFree-mp3-albums.comLeukespellen.beIgry.by&lt;span&gt;	&lt;/span&gt;Hrajted.czlege.dkSpilleland.comGladespil.dkTitter.dk&lt;br&gt;Funnygames.co.ukTessagames.co.ukFunnycoloring.comJeuxgratuits.frTitter.frIeuxdroles.fr&lt;br&gt;Universdesjeux.frColoriage.orgWyspagier.plmultumgier.plFlashgierki.plTitter.plJakoloruje.plBrincar.pt&lt;br&gt;Titter.pt&lt;span&gt;	&lt;/span&gt;Desenhos.ptSkojspel.seJocuri.net1001jocuri.comJoacajocuri.roTitter.roIgriigri.ru&lt;br&gt;Igrytessy.ruHry.netTitter.esIuegoswapos.esChulojuegos.comDiibujos.orgFunspiele.chOyunyolu.net&lt;br&gt;Oyunlaradasi.comMary.comGamesclub.comJocjogos.comJogosloucos.com.brJogarlegal.com.br&lt;br&gt;Goodgame.co.in&lt;span&gt;	&lt;/span&gt;Minigame.com.tw
 Minigame.com.cnWarda.comSpiel.deSpielkarussell.de 
Tessaspiele.deJetzmalen.deTitter.grJatekok.netTitter.huGiocare.itIsoladeigiochi.itUniversodelgioco.it&lt;br&gt;Colorare.itSpeeleiland.nlSpelletje.nlTitter.nlNukleuren.nlSpille.noMinespill.comGratisspill.no,&amp;nbsp;www.applifier.com&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;]]></restrictions>
			<tc>
			</tc>
			<categories>Mobile Apps,Games</categories>
			<mobile_tags>Android, Android Tablet</mobile_tags>
			<countries> AR, AU, AT, BY, BO, BR, CA, CL, CN, CO, DO, EC, SV, FR, DE, GT, HN, HK, IT, JP, KZ, KR, KG, MO, MX, NL, NI, PA, PY, PE, PL, RU, ES, CH, TW, TR, UA, GB, US, UY, VE</countries>
			<media_types>Display, In App, Mobile Display, Pops</media_types>
			<languages> eng</languages>
			<tracking_duration>45</tracking_duration>
			<deep_links>0</deep_links>
			<date_created>2013-08-02 03:34:22</date_created>
			<date_updated>2015-01-24 10:20:14</date_updated>
		</program>
		<program>
			<id>99171</id>
			<name>CheapInsurance.com - ZIP submit (EXCLUSIVE) - US - Non Incentivi</name>
			<url>http://www.cheapinsurance.com/</url>
			<association_status>Approved</association_status>
			<description><![CDATA[Consumers can get free auto insurance quotes.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;User Flow: The pixel fires when the user submits the zip code.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;]]></description>
			<restrictions><![CDATA[Traffic Accepted: 18+, US Only&lt;span style="font-size:11px;"&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11px;"&gt;The
usage of Creative/texts (banners, e-mail, text ads etc) that were not provided
by the advertiser, will only be allowed upon the advertiser's approval.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Pop
traffic is allowed only upon advertiser's approval and capping.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;span style="font-size:11pt;font-family:Calibri, 'sans-serif';"&gt;Incentivized
traffic is not allowed, no CL, no VC.&lt;br&gt;&lt;/span&gt;]]></restrictions>
			<tc>
			</tc>
			<categories>Insurance,Lead Generation</categories>
			<mobile_tags>
			</mobile_tags>
			<countries> US</countries>
			<media_types><![CDATA[Display, Email, GDN, Host &amp; Post, Mobile Display, Pops, Search, Social]]></media_types>
			<languages> eng</languages>
			<tracking_duration>30</tracking_duration>
			<deep_links>0</deep_links>
			<date_created>2013-08-06 11:21:42</date_created>
			<date_updated>2014-07-28 11:53:09</date_updated>
		</program>
		<program>
			<id>101651</id>
			<name>War Thunder Extended SOI EN</name>
			<url>www.matomy.com</url>
			<association_status>Approved</association_status>
			<logo>http://network.adsmarket.com/site/StoredImage?cid=308fc80b</logo>
			<description><![CDATA[War Thunder offers a highly detailed and personalized aviation experience,&amp;nbsp;giving players access to hundreds models of planes with detailed cockpits,&amp;nbsp;dozens of upgradeable weapons, and flying skills that can be honed and&amp;nbsp;improved with each mission. Thanks to the game&rsquo;s painstaking attention to detail,&amp;nbsp;you&rsquo;ll truly feel like a World War II fighter pilot&amp;nbsp;as you plunge into battle.&lt;br&gt;valid lead criteria: user must fill in user name, password*2 , email and capcha, download and login to the installer - SOI]]></description>
			<restrictions><![CDATA[new publishers may start with 100 daily leads per campaign until further feedback,only traffic from designated country is allowed no You tube, no video banners with sounds, &amp;nbsp;Leads that will result in less than 5% active users will be considered as incentivized and will not be paid.&lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11.0pt;font-family:&amp;quot;Calibri&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;sans-serif&amp;quot;;
mso-fareast-font-family:Calibri;mso-fareast-theme-font:minor-latin;mso-bidi-font-family:
&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;;mso-ansi-language:EN-US;mso-fareast-language:EN-US;
mso-bidi-language:HE"&gt;In order to run this offer with Adwords, please contact
your account manager&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;]]></restrictions>
			<tc>
			</tc>
			<categories>Games</categories>
			<mobile_tags>
			</mobile_tags>
			<countries> AU, CA, NZ, GB, US</countries>
			<media_types>Display, GDN, Social</media_types>
			<languages>
			</languages>
			<tracking_duration>45</tracking_duration>
			<deep_links>0</deep_links>
			<date_created>2013-08-28 09:54:08</date_created>
			<date_updated>2014-11-03 08:45:56</date_updated>
		</program>
		<program>
			<id>105331</id>
			<name>SATA Airlines CPS Intl' Non Incent WEB</name>
			<url>www.matomy.com</url>
			<association_status>Approved</association_status>
			<logo>http://network.adsmarket.com/site/StoredImage?cid=2c76d6c6</logo>
			<description><![CDATA[&lt;u&gt;&lt;b&gt;Offer Review:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/b&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;br&gt;SATA offers a broad range of international flights connections with a choice of a wide range of new and lowest fares, one-way and return fares to over 20 European and North America destinations, such as Munich/Paris/London/Lisbon/Boston/Toronto. We also have a large range of partnerships covering over 100 destinations on medium/long-haul flights covering all major cities in Europe/USA/Canada/Africa and Russia.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;b&gt;Affiliate Benefits:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/b&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;br&gt;90-day action referral period. &lt;br&gt;Attractive commissions.&lt;br&gt;Valid for all class reservations&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;b&gt;User Flow:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/b&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;br&gt;Revenue-Share Program: &lt;br&gt;3.0% Rev-Share for 90 Days, for unlimited number of purchases.&lt;br&gt;-A sale amount is the total sale amount on fares, excluding taxes.&lt;br&gt;-May offer a special CPA rate for different routes&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;b&gt;Typical Demographics:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/b&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;br&gt;By gender:&lt;br&gt;Male: 45%&lt;br&gt;female: 55%&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;By device:&lt;br&gt;desktop: 85%&lt;br&gt;Tablet: 10%&lt;br&gt;Phone: 5%&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;By country:&lt;br&gt;PT: 40%&lt;br&gt;US: 20%&lt;br&gt;CA: 15%&lt;br&gt;DE: 10%&lt;br&gt;ES/FR/UK: 5%&lt;br&gt;]]></description>
			<restrictions><![CDATA[SEM Restrictions:&lt;br&gt;No SEM Brand Bidding:&lt;br&gt;The word SATA, and conjugation of words with 
SATA are not allowed. Also AZORES Express is the brand of our branch in 
USA, so, also not allowed.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;* SATA * &lt;br&gt;SATA International&lt;br&gt;SATA Azores&lt;br&gt;AZORES Express&lt;br&gt;SATA Express&lt;br&gt;SATA Air A&ccedil;ores&lt;br&gt;SATA Imagine&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Valid Conversion Criteria: &lt;br&gt;a Valid sale occurs once a user customizes a flight search on the site, Inputs billing information&lt;br&gt;and completes a reservation, Booking and purchase.&lt;br&gt;Commissions will not be paid for returned sales or sales made from an invalid/stolen credit card.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;]]></restrictions>
			<tc>
			</tc>
			<categories>Travel</categories>
			<mobile_tags>
			</mobile_tags>
			<countries> BE, CA, DK, FI, FR, DE, IE, LU, NL, NO, PT, ES, SE, GB, US</countries>
			<media_types>
			</media_types>
			<languages> heb</languages>
			<tracking_duration>90</tracking_duration>
			<deep_links>1</deep_links>
			<date_created>2013-10-08 08:48:46</date_created>
			<date_updated>2014-11-03 08:27:20</date_updated>
		</program>
		<program>
			<id>110151</id>
			<name>Classmates.com - US - NON INCENTIVIZED</name>
			<url>http://www.classmates.com/</url>
			<association_status>Approved</association_status>
			<logo>http://network.adsmarket.com/site/StoredImage?cid=2b1df37f</logo>
			<description><![CDATA[Classmates is the online home for your high school class. With the largest directory of high schools and class lists available anywhere, covering 57 million people and including maiden names, Classmates makes finding, reconnecting and staying up with your high school class fun and easy. Classmates also has over 200,000 digitized high school yearbooks available for you to view and share photos.

&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;User Flow: 2nd page submit + including a 2nd pixel on purchase for optimization]]></description>
			<restrictions><![CDATA[THIS OFFER CANNOT BE INCENTIVIZED.Search engine marketers are NOT permitted to bid on nor utilize trademarked brand name keywords such as or any derivations thereof.No utilization of trademarked/branded terms in ad copy nor purchasing such names in domains (i.e., etc.).Trademarked/branded terms should be selected for Negative match. Landing/jump pages created should not resemble the Advertiser's site(s) to give the impression it is the actual site.A publisher who will use Facebook to promote this program will not be compensated for generated commissions and will risk suspension from Matomy Market.Any violations will not be paid for and may result in termination of your account.The usage of Creative/texts (banners, e-mail, text ads etc) that were not provided by the advertiser, will only be allowed upon the advertiser's approval.No VC, No Content Locking.&amp;nbsp;Pop traffic must be approved.Valid Lead Criteria: 18+Traffic Accepted: USDistribution Methods Allowed: Display&lt;br&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11.0pt;font-family:&amp;quot;Calibri&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;sans-serif&amp;quot;;
mso-fareast-font-family:Calibri;mso-fareast-theme-font:minor-latin;mso-bidi-font-family:
&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;;mso-ansi-language:EN-US;mso-fareast-language:EN-US;
mso-bidi-language:AR-SA"&gt;In order to run this offer with Adwords, please
contact your account manager.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11.0pt;
font-family:&amp;quot;Calibri&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;sans-serif&amp;quot;;mso-fareast-font-family:Calibri;mso-fareast-theme-font:
minor-latin;mso-bidi-font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;;mso-ansi-language:EN-US;
mso-fareast-language:EN-US;mso-bidi-language:AR-SA"&gt;"&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;]]></restrictions>
			<tc>
			</tc>
			<categories>Lead Generation</categories>
			<mobile_tags>
			</mobile_tags>
			<countries> US</countries>
			<media_types>Display, Search, Social</media_types>
			<languages>
			</languages>
			<tracking_duration>30</tracking_duration>
			<deep_links>0</deep_links>
			<date_created>2013-11-19 10:03:39</date_created>
			<date_updated>2014-09-16 09:57:03</date_updated>
		</program>
		<program>
			<id>112621</id>
			<name>HTML 5 Games - CA/DE/US/UK/AU - Incentivized</name>
			<url>http://games.softgames.de</url>
			<association_status>Approved</association_status>
			<logo>http://network.adsmarket.com/site/StoredImage?cid=2c64fd7a</logo>
			<description><![CDATA[Offer Review:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;HTML5 Games&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;User Flow:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;pixel fires after 2 minute play&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Typical Demographics:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;All]]></description>
			<restrictions><![CDATA[&lt;br&gt;new publishers can start with 200 daily leads until further feedback&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;]]></restrictions>
			<tc>
			</tc>
			<categories>Mobile Apps,Incentivized</categories>
			<mobile_tags>iOS, Android, Windows Phone</mobile_tags>
			<countries> AU, AT, CA, FR, DE, IT, NO, ES, CH, GB, US</countries>
			<media_types>Content Locking, Incentivized</media_types>
			<languages>
			</languages>
			<tracking_duration>45</tracking_duration>
			<deep_links>0</deep_links>
			<date_created>2013-12-10 09:48:11</date_created>
			<date_updated>2014-10-14 04:06:08</date_updated>
		</program>
		<program>
			<id>113761</id>
			<name>FunkPlay - Int' - Non Incentivized - OLFA - Movies</name>
			<url>www.matomy.com</url>
			<association_status>Approved</association_status>
			<logo>http://network.adsmarket.com/site/StoredImage?cid=383f8841</logo>
			<description><![CDATA[Offer Review:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;Join hundreds of thousands of satisfied members of FunkPlay who became 
tired of searching for Movies &amp;amp; TV shows online, and now enjoy the 
hottest new Movies &amp;amp; TV shows and timeless classics on our site.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Affiliate Benefits:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;Higher rates available for high-performing affiliates, at the advertiser's discretion.Hot offer with incredible conversion rates, strong landing page and pre-lander design, with a wide spread of geo's internationally which can be found at the link below.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;User Flow:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;User registers with basic personal information to create a free account, then submits valid payment&lt;br&gt;details for a free trial membership period to the service. CPA conversion will fire once user submits valid payment details.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;b&gt;Publisher Payouts:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;http://www.tsxnrey.com/i/JMedia/ratepergeo&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Typical Demographics:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;All]]></description>
			<restrictions><![CDATA[&lt;b&gt;Publisher Payouts:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;http://www.tsxnrey.com/i/JMedia/ratepergeo&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Creative Guidelines: In addition to the materials supplied by Advertiser, Matomy and its publishers may use their own creative materials, including generic "Play Now" buttons and pre-landers instead of the "Step 0" page provided. In any event, all traffic must lead to/through the standard "Step 1" page provided by Advertiser.&lt;br&gt;]]></restrictions>
			<tc>
			</tc>
			<categories>Entertainment</categories>
			<mobile_tags>
			</mobile_tags>
			<countries> AX, AD, AU, AT, BE, CA, CL, CY, DK, FI, FR, DE, GI, GR, GG, HK, IS, IE, IM, IT, JM, JP, JE, KW, LU, MX, MC, NL, NZ, NO, PT, PR, SG, ES, SE, CH, TT, TR, AE, GB, US</countries>
			<media_types>Display, In App, Mobile Display, Pops</media_types>
			<languages>
			</languages>
			<tracking_duration>45</tracking_duration>
			<deep_links>0</deep_links>
			<date_created>2013-12-22 05:50:01</date_created>
			<date_updated>2014-08-07 06:04:42</date_updated>
		</program>
		<program>
			<id>116591</id>
			<name>OGame Int'l Non Incent</name>
			<url>http://us.ogame.gameforge.com/</url>
			<association_status>Approved</association_status>
			<logo>http://network.adsmarket.com/site/StoredImage?cid=2df82147</logo>
			<description><![CDATA[&lt;b&gt;Browser game&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With over 30 million fans worldwide, OGame is one of the most successful browser titles of all time. Set in the vast reaches of outer space, OGame is a multiplayer online real-time strategy game that gives players the chance to research powerful technologies, colonize planets, and amass giant armadas as they mine and trade precious resources.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;b&gt;No Cost and No Downloads&lt;/b&gt;: OGame is browser-based and completely free-to-play. Whether you use a PC or a Mac, all you need is an internet connection to get started on your intergalactic empire.&lt;b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;b&gt;User Flow:&lt;/b&gt;Username, email, password, register (Single Opt-In)]]></description>
			<restrictions><![CDATA[&lt;b style="margin:0px;padding:0px;color:rgb(102,102,102);"&gt;Program is under budget, please contact your Matomy account manager if you would like to run this program.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;b style="margin:0px;padding:0px;color:rgb(102,102,102);"&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;b style="margin:0px;padding:0px;color:rgb(102,102,102);"&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight:normal;background-color:rgb(255,255,255);"&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="margin:0px;padding:0px;color:rgb(102,102,102);"&gt;site unders allowed&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;b style="margin:0px;padding:0px;color:rgb(102,102,102);"&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight:normal;background-color:rgb(255,255,255);"&gt;"Blacklisted site (banners are not to be placed on this site): Movshare.net"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;]]></restrictions>
			<tc>
			</tc>
			<categories>Games</categories>
			<mobile_tags>
			</mobile_tags>
			<countries> AU, AT, BE, CA, HR, CZ, DK, FR, DE, GR, HU, IE, IT, JP, MX, NZ, PL, PT, RO, RU, SK, ES, SE, CH, TR, GB, US</countries>
			<media_types>Display, GDN, Social</media_types>
			<languages>
			</languages>
			<tracking_duration>1</tracking_duration>
			<deep_links>0</deep_links>
			<date_created>2014-01-24 03:33:04</date_created>
			<date_updated>2015-01-02 12:45:45</date_updated>
		</program>
		<program>
			<id>120041</id>
			<name>VideoStripe - Intl' - Non Incent - OLFA</name>
			<url>www.videostripe.com</url>
			<association_status>Approved</association_status>
			<logo>http://network.adsmarket.com/site/StoredImage?cid=2fa7bf2f</logo>
			<description><![CDATA[&lt;span style="font-weight: bold; text-decoration: underline;"&gt;EXCLUSIVE RATES &lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;u&gt;Offer Review:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;br&gt;Video-on-demand service containing only legal contents attractive up-to-date movie database&lt;br&gt;Easy sign up with a 2-week free trial, after which the account can be prolonged for $49,99 per month&lt;br&gt;24/7 professional support at customers disposal&lt;br&gt;no binding periods &ndash; account cancellation in a few easy steps account fully free of advertisements&lt;br&gt;approaching customers all over the world&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Affiliate Benefits:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;br&gt;International Campaign, amazing rate! Higher rates available for high-performing affiliates, at the advertiser's discretion.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;b&gt;User Flow:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;br&gt;User submits valid email, password and password confirmation. User then submits valid payment details&lt;br&gt;to sign up for a free trial. CPA conversion occurs once user submits valid payment details.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;b&gt;Typical Demographics:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;br&gt;All&lt;br&gt;]]></description>
			<restrictions><![CDATA[&lt;p&gt;&lt;b style="margin: 0px; padding: 0px; text-rendering: optimizelegibility; color: rgb(102, 102, 102);"&gt;Please note: New publishers are limited to a daily cap of 40 leads a day until approved.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;b style="margin: 0px; padding: 0px; text-rendering: optimizelegibility; color: rgb(102, 102, 102);"&gt;&lt;br style="margin: 0px; padding: 0px; text-rendering: optimizelegibility;"&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;Traffic: Worldwide (except for the following geos:&amp;nbsp;&lt;span style="font-size: 7.5pt; font-family: Helvetica, sans-serif;"&gt;IN,
IR, PL, IN, CN, ID, KZ, NG, PK, EG, MA, KW, FJ, BW, CW, TZ, MV, PE, GT, CO, MY,
RU.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;Mobile: exclude traffic from Opera Mini&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;u&gt;Valid Conversion Criteria: &lt;/u&gt;&lt;br&gt;User submits valid email, password and password confirmation. User then submits valid payment details&lt;br&gt;to sign up for a free trial. CPA conversion occurs once user submits valid payment details.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;]]></restrictions>
			<tc>
			</tc>
			<categories>Entertainment,Mobile Optimized</categories>
			<mobile_tags>3G, WiFi</mobile_tags>
			<countries> AF, AX, AL, DZ, AS, AD, AO, AI, A1, AQ, AG, AR, AM, AW, AP, AU, AT, AZ, BS, BH, BD, BB, BY, BE, BZ, BJ, BM, BT, BO, BQ, BA, BV, BR, IO, BN, BG, BF, BI, KH, CM, CA, CV, KY, CF, TD, CL, CX, CC, KM, CG, CD, CK, CR, CI, HR, CU, CY, CZ, DK, DJ, DM, DO, TP, EC, SV, GQ, ER, EE, ET, EU, FK, FO, FI, FR, GF, PF, TF, GA, GM, GE, DE, GH, GI, GR, GL, GD, GP, GU, GG, GN, GW, GY, HT, HM, HN, HK, HU, IS, IQ, IE, IM, IL, IT, JM, JP, JE, JO, KE, KI, KP, KR, KG, LA, LV, LB, LS, LR, LY, LI, LT, LU, MO, MK, MG, MW, ML, MT, MH, MQ, MR, MU, YT, MX, FM, MD, MC, MN, ME, MS, MZ, MM, NA, NR, NP, NL, AN, NC, NZ, NI, NE, NU, NF, MP, NO, OM, PW, PS, PA, PG, PY, PH, PN, PT, PR, QA, RE, RO, RW, SH, KN, LC, MF, PM, VC, WS, SM, ST, A2, SA, SN, RS, SC, SL, SG, SK, SI, SB, SO, ZA, GS, ES, LK, SD, SR, SJ, SZ, SE, CH, SY, TW, TJ, TH, TL, TG, TK, TO, TT, TN, TR, TM, TC, TV, UG, UA, AE, GB, US, UM, UY, UZ, VU, VA, VE, VN, VG, VI, WF, EH, YE, ZM, ZW</countries>
			<media_types>Display, In App, Mobile Display, Pops</media_types>
			<languages>
			</languages>
			<tracking_duration>45</tracking_duration>
			<deep_links>0</deep_links>
			<date_created>2014-02-24 07:15:37</date_created>
			<date_updated>2015-02-25 07:44:53</date_updated>
		</program>
		<program>
			<id>120051</id>
			<name>VideoStripe - Intl' - Incent - OLFA</name>
			<url>www.videostripe.com</url>
			<association_status>Approved</association_status>
			<logo>http://network.adsmarket.com/site/StoredImage?cid=2fa95e93</logo>
			<description><![CDATA[&lt;span style="font-weight: bold; text-decoration: underline;"&gt;EXCLUSIVE RATES &lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;b&gt;&lt;u&gt;Offer Review:&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;
Video-on-demand service containing only legal contents attractive up-to-date movie database&lt;br&gt;Easy sign up with a 2-week free trial, after which the account can be prolonged for $49,99 per month&lt;br&gt;24/7 professional support at customers disposal&lt;br&gt;no binding periods &ndash; account cancellation in a few easy steps account fully free of advertisements&lt;br&gt;approaching customers all over the world&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;u&gt;&lt;b&gt;Affiliate Benefits:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;br&gt;
International Campaign, amazing rate! Higher rates available for high-performing affiliates, at the advertiser's discretion.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;b&gt;&lt;u&gt;User Flow:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;
User submits valid email, password and password confirmation. User then submits valid payment details&lt;br&gt;
to sign up for a free trial. CPA conversion occurs once user submits valid payment details.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;u&gt;&lt;b&gt;Typical Demographics:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;
All]]></description>
			<restrictions><![CDATA[&lt;b&gt;Each publisher running this program is limited to a daily cap of 40 leads until given feedback!&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Traffic from Worldwide&lt;span style="color: rgb(102, 102, 102); background-color: rgb(255, 255, 255);"&gt;&amp;nbsp;(except for the following geos:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 7.5pt; font-family: Helvetica, sans-serif;"&gt;IN,
IR, PL, IN, CN, ID, KZ, NG, PK, EG, MA, KW, FJ, BW, CW, TZ, MV, PE, GT, CO, MY,
RU&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p style="margin: 0px; padding: 0px; text-rendering: optimizelegibility; color: rgb(102, 102, 102);"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgb(102, 102, 102); background-color: rgb(255, 255, 255);"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;Mobile: exclude traffic from Opera Mini&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;b&gt;Valid Conversion Criteria: &lt;/b&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;br&gt;User submits valid email, password and password confirmation. User then submits valid payment details&lt;br&gt;
to sign up for a free trial. CPA conversion occurs once user submits valid payment details.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;]]></restrictions>
			<tc>
			</tc>
			<categories>Entertainment,Incentivized,Mobile Optimized</categories>
			<mobile_tags>
			</mobile_tags>
			<countries> AF, AX, AL, DZ, AS, AD, AO, AI, A1, AQ, AG, AR, AM, AW, AP, AU, AT, AZ, BS, BH, BD, BB, BY, BE, BZ, BJ, BM, BT, BO, BQ, BA, BV, BR, IO, BN, BG, BF, BI, KH, CM, CA, CV, KY, CF, TD, CL, CX, CC, KM, CG, CD, CK, CR, CI, HR, CU, CY, CZ, DK, DJ, DM, DO, TP, EC, SV, GQ, ER, EE, ET, EU, FK, FO, FI, FR, GF, PF, TF, GA, GM, GE, DE, GH, GI, GR, GL, GD, GP, GU, GG, GN, GW, GY, HT, HM, HN, HK, HU, IS, IQ, IE, IM, IL, IT, JM, JP, JE, JO, KE, KI, KP, KR, KG, LA, LV, LB, LS, LR, LY, LI, LT, LU, MO, MK, MG, MW, ML, MT, MH, MQ, MR, MU, YT, MX, FM, MD, MC, MN, ME, MS, MZ, MM, NA, NR, NP, NL, AN, NC, NZ, NI, NE, NU, NF, MP, NO, OM, PW, PS, PA, PG, PY, PH, PN, PT, PR, QA, RE, RO, RW, SH, KN, LC, MF, PM, VC, WS, SM, ST, A2, SA, SN, RS, SC, SL, SG, SK, SI, SB, SO, ZA, GS, ES, LK, SD, SR, SJ, SZ, SE, CH, SY, TW, TJ, TH, TL, TG, TK, TO, TT, TN, TR, TM, TC, TV, UG, UA, AE, GB, US, UM, UY, UZ, VU, VA, VE, VN, VG, VI, WF, EH, YE, ZM, ZW</countries>
			<media_types>Content Locking, Display, In App, Incentivized, Mobile Display, Pops</media_types>
			<languages>
			</languages>
			<tracking_duration>45</tracking_duration>
			<deep_links>0</deep_links>
			<date_created>2014-02-24 07:17:19</date_created>
			<date_updated>2015-02-25 08:09:42</date_updated>
		</program>
		<program>
			<id>121791</id>
			<name>Vittalia - Tiers - Non Incentivized - LP's</name>
			<url>www.matomy.com</url>
			<association_status>Approved</association_status>
			<logo>http://network.adsmarket.com/site/StoredImage?cid=3096459b</logo>
			<description><![CDATA[&lt;u&gt;&lt;b&gt;Publisher Rates:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;br&gt;

http://www.tsxnrey.com/i/Vittalia/Country%2016.7.14.pdf&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Offer Review:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;Popular downloads products for the everyday PC user including Media Players, Torrents, Codepacks, Antivirus and more!&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Affiliate Benefits:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;High-converting array of products available in a variety of hot countries. &lt;br&gt;Higher rates available for high-performing affiliates, at the advertiser's discretion.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;User Flow:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;User clicks to download, then installs product on their computer.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Typical Demographics:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;All&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;]]></description>
			<restrictions><![CDATA[&lt;u&gt;&lt;b&gt;Publisher Rates:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;br&gt;

Traffic Allowed from specific country only according to the attached link:&lt;br&gt;http://www.tsxnrey.com/i/Vittalia/Country%2016.7.14.pdf&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;No Incentivized Traffic&lt;br&gt;No Virtual Currency Traffic &lt;br&gt;No Co-Registration Marketing &amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;No Content Locking &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Valid Conversion Criteria: &lt;br&gt;User clicks to download, then installs product on their computer. Valid Conversion fires upon&lt;br&gt;successful installation, regardless of any bundled accepted along the installer path.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Creative Guidelines: &lt;br&gt;In addition to the creative materials supplied by Advertiser, Matomy and its Publishers may use&lt;br&gt;additional creative materials.]]></restrictions>
			<tc>
			</tc>
			<categories>Downloads</categories>
			<mobile_tags>
			</mobile_tags>
			<countries> DZ, BE, BR, DK, EG, FI, FR, DE, IN, IQ, JP, JO, KW, NL, PK, PE, RU, SA, ES, SE, TH, TN, AE, GB, US, VE</countries>
			<media_types>Display, Pops</media_types>
			<languages>
			</languages>
			<tracking_duration>45</tracking_duration>
			<deep_links>0</deep_links>
			<date_created>2014-03-17 06:07:00</date_created>
			<date_updated>2015-02-11 03:50:51</date_updated>
		</program>
		<program>
			<id>122901</id>
			<name>Asian Date - INTL - NON INCENTIVIZED</name>
			<url>www.asiandate.com</url>
			<association_status>Approved</association_status>
			<logo>http://network.adsmarket.com/site/StoredImage?cid=30b37aa3</logo>
			<description><![CDATA[Users can set-up an account and be introduced to lovely Asian ladies.&lt;br&gt;User Flow: &amp;nbsp;Registration on 2nd page.]]></description>
			<restrictions><![CDATA[THIS OFFER CANNOT BE INCENTIVIZED.Search engine marketers are NOT permitted to bid on nor utilize trademarked brand name keywords such as or any derivations thereof.No utilization of trademarked/branded terms in ad copy nor purchasing such names in domains (i.e., etc.).Trademarked/branded terms should be selected for Negative match.Landing/jump pages created should not resemble the Advertiser's site(s) to give the impression it is the actual site.A publisher who will use Facebook to promote this program will not be compensated for generated commissions and will risk suspension from Matomy Market.Any violations will not be paid for and may result in termination of your account.The usage of Creative/texts (banners, e-mail, text ads etc) that were not provided by the advertiser, will only be allowed upon the advertiser's approval.&lt;b&gt;This program is under budget; please contact your affiliate manager to get more information.&lt;/b&gt;No VC, No Content Locking. Pop traffic must be approved.Valid Lead Criteria: 18+.Traffic Accepted: US, CA, AU, UK, MY, SG, HK, JP, KR, AT, FR, NL, CH.&amp;nbsp;Distribution Methods Allowed: &lt;b&gt;Please see campaign descriptions for specifics. &amp;nbsp;&lt;/b&gt;]]></restrictions>
			<tc>
			</tc>
			<categories>Dating</categories>
			<mobile_tags>
			</mobile_tags>
			<countries> AU, AT, CA, FR, HK, JP, KR, MY, NL, SG, CH, GB, US</countries>
			<media_types>Display, Email</media_types>
			<languages>
			</languages>
			<tracking_duration>30</tracking_duration>
			<deep_links>0</deep_links>
			<date_created>2014-03-25 15:38:06</date_created>
			<date_updated>2014-08-07 15:33:25</date_updated>
		</program>
		<program>
			<id>123472</id>
			<name>Aura Kingdom - US/UK/AU/NL/Nordics - Non Incent</name>
			<url>www.matomy.com</url>
			<association_status>Approved</association_status>
			<logo>http://network.adsmarket.com/site/StoredImage?cid=395b7d9d</logo>
			<description><![CDATA[&lt;b&gt;Download game&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;p style="margin-bottom:.0001pt;"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Free-to-play
anime style MMORPG&lt;br&gt;
An all new game - release in January 2014!!&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;b&gt;User flow: &lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;SOI, register for game&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;]]></description>
			<restrictions><![CDATA[This program is under budget; please contact your affiliate manager to get more information.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;]]></restrictions>
			<tc>
			</tc>
			<categories>Games</categories>
			<mobile_tags>
			</mobile_tags>
			<countries> AU, DK, FI, NL, NO, SE, GB, US</countries>
			<media_types><![CDATA[Display, Email, GDN, Host &amp; Post, Pops, Social]]></media_types>
			<languages>
			</languages>
			<tracking_duration>45</tracking_duration>
			<deep_links>0</deep_links>
			<date_created>2014-04-01 09:25:19</date_created>
			<date_updated>2015-01-12 04:01:21</date_updated>
		</program>
		<program>
			<id>123762</id>
			<name>Funding Point - EXCLUSIVE -US - Non Incentivized</name>
			<url>https://funding-point.com</url>
			<association_status>Approved</association_status>
			<logo>http://network.adsmarket.com/site/StoredImage?cid=30f7b5d0</logo>
			<description><![CDATA[Consumers can borrow short to long term loans up to 2,500 pounds from Funding Point! This offer pays on a second page submit&lt;br&gt;Conversion Point: 2nd page&lt;br&gt;Distributional Methods Allowed: Email,&amp;nbsp;&lt;span style="color:rgb(51,51,51);font-family:verdana;font-size:12px;"&gt;display and social traffic Sales occur in real time&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;span style="color:rgb(51,51,51);font-family:verdana;font-size:12px;"&gt;Traffic Accepted: 18+,This is US offer only NO INCENT TRAFFIC&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;]]></description>
			<restrictions><![CDATA[&lt;br&gt;&lt;p&gt;The
usage of Creative/texts (banners, e-mail, text ads etc) that were not provided
by the advertiser, will only be allowed upon the advertiser's approval.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Pop
traffic is allowed only upon advertiser's approval and capping.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p style="color:rgb(51,51,51);font-family:verdana;font-size:12px;"&gt;You must redirect all traffic through your own redirection process if you are marketing this offer via email! Unless otherwise noted in the offer description none of the offers may be incentivized&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="color:rgb(51,51,51);font-family:verdana;font-size:12px;"&gt;&amp;nbsp;Offer is uncapped.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;]]></restrictions>
			<tc>
			</tc>
			<categories>Finance</categories>
			<mobile_tags>
			</mobile_tags>
			<countries> US</countries>
			<media_types>Display, Email, Pops, GDN, Social</media_types>
			<languages> eng</languages>
			<tracking_duration>30</tracking_duration>
			<deep_links>0</deep_links>
			<date_created>2014-04-03 15:21:13</date_created>
			<date_updated>2014-04-14 11:02:10</date_updated>
		</program>
		<program>
			<id>126381</id>
			<name>Brazilian Date - INTL - NON INCENTIVIZED</name>
			<url>http://brazilians.com-2014.org/web/</url>
			<association_status>Approved</association_status>
			<logo>http://network.adsmarket.com/site/StoredImage?cid=32dccad7</logo>
			<description><![CDATA[&lt;span style="font-size:11pt;font-family:Calibri, 'sans-serif';"&gt;Users can set-up an account and be introduced to
lovely Brazilian ladies.&lt;br&gt;User Flow: &amp;nbsp;Registration on 2nd page.&lt;/span&gt;]]></description>
			<restrictions><![CDATA[&lt;span style="color:rgb(102,102,102);background-color:rgb(255,255,255);"&gt;THIS OFFER CANNOT BE INCENTIVIZED.Search engine marketers are NOT permitted to bid on nor utilize trademarked brand name keywords such as or any derivations thereof.No utilization of trademarked/branded terms in ad copy nor purchasing such names in domains (i.e., etc.).Trademarked/branded terms should be selected for Negative match.Landing/jump pages created should not resemble the Advertiser's site(s) to give the impression it is the actual site.A publisher who will use Facebook to promote this program will not be compensated for generated commissions and will risk suspension from Matomy Market.Any violations will not be paid for and may result in termination of your account.The usage of Creative/texts (banners, e-mail, text ads etc) that were not provided by the advertiser, will only be allowed upon the advertiser's approval.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;b style="margin:0px;padding:0px;color:rgb(102,102,102);"&gt;This program is under budget; please contact your affiliate manager to get more information.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;span style="color:rgb(102,102,102);background-color:rgb(255,255,255);"&gt;No VC, No Content Locking. Pop traffic must be approved.Valid Lead Criteria: 18+.Traffic Accepted: US, AU, CA, NO, SE, ZA, DK, BE.&amp;nbsp;Distribution Methods Allowed:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;b style="margin:0px;padding:0px;color:rgb(102,102,102);"&gt;Email Only. &amp;nbsp;&lt;/b&gt;]]></restrictions>
			<tc>
			</tc>
			<categories>Dating</categories>
			<mobile_tags>
			</mobile_tags>
			<countries> AU, BE, CA, DK, NO, ZA, SE, GB, US</countries>
			<media_types>Display, Email</media_types>
			<languages> eng</languages>
			<tracking_duration>30</tracking_duration>
			<deep_links>0</deep_links>
			<date_created>2014-04-29 16:40:32</date_created>
			<date_updated>2014-08-07 14:31:51</date_updated>
		</program>
		<program>
			<id>126401</id>
			<name>Russian Date  - INTL - NON INCENTIVIZED</name>
			<url>http://russians.com-2014.org/web/</url>
			<association_status>Approved</association_status>
			<logo>http://network.adsmarket.com/site/StoredImage?cid=32de6a3b</logo>
			<description><![CDATA[&lt;span style="font-size:11pt;font-family:Calibri, 'sans-serif';"&gt;Users can set-up an account and be introduced to lovely
Russian ladies.&lt;br&gt;
User Flow: &amp;nbsp;Registration on 2nd page.&lt;/span&gt;]]></description>
			<restrictions><![CDATA[&lt;span style="color:rgb(102,102,102);background-color:rgb(255,255,255);"&gt;THIS OFFER CANNOT BE INCENTIVIZED.Search engine marketers are NOT permitted to bid on nor utilize trademarked brand name keywords such as or any derivations thereof.No utilization of trademarked/branded terms in ad copy nor purchasing such names in domains (i.e., etc.).Trademarked/branded terms should be selected for Negative match.Landing/jump pages created should not resemble the Advertiser's site(s) to give the impression it is the actual site.A publisher who will use Facebook to promote this program will not be compensated for generated commissions and will risk suspension from Matomy Market.Any violations will not be paid for and may result in termination of your account.The usage of Creative/texts (banners, e-mail, text ads etc) that were not provided by the advertiser, will only be allowed upon the advertiser's approval.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;b style="margin:0px;padding:0px;color:rgb(102,102,102);"&gt;This program is under budget; please contact your affiliate manager to get more information.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;span style="color:rgb(102,102,102);background-color:rgb(255,255,255);"&gt;No VC, No Content Locking. Pop traffic must be approved.Valid Lead Criteria: 18+.Traffic Accepted: US, CA, AU, NZ, UK, NO, DK,SE, CH, NL, ZA, BR, MX, AQ, TR, AE, AT, HR, CY, FI, HU, IS, IL, MT, PT, SK, ES, EE, LV .&amp;nbsp;Distribution Methods Allowed:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;b style="margin:0px;padding:0px;color:rgb(102,102,102);"&gt;Email, Display. &amp;nbsp;&lt;/b&gt;]]></restrictions>
			<tc>
			</tc>
			<categories>Dating</categories>
			<mobile_tags>
			</mobile_tags>
			<countries> AU, AT, BR, CA, HR, CY, DK, EE, FI, HU, IS, IL, LV, MT, MX, NL, NZ, NO, PT, QA, SK, ZA, ES, SE, CH, TR, AE, GB, US</countries>
			<media_types>Display, Email</media_types>
			<languages> eng</languages>
			<tracking_duration>30</tracking_duration>
			<deep_links>0</deep_links>
			<date_created>2014-04-29 16:52:27</date_created>
			<date_updated>2014-08-07 15:34:19</date_updated>
		</program>
		<program>
			<id>126611</id>
			<name>ShoeDazzle - US - NON INCENT</name>
			<url>http://www.shoedazzle.com/</url>
			<association_status>Approved</association_status>
			<logo>http://network.adsmarket.com/site/StoredImage?cid=330d788f</logo>
			<description><![CDATA[Joining ShoeDazzle is free and takes only a few minutes. Simply take the style quiz and create a sign-in. Members get access to some of their best selling styles right away, and within 24 hours, ShoeDazzle will create a personalized showroom filled with on- trend shoes and handbags. Members will also be able to shop our stylist-curated boutiques and lookbooks.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;User Flow: Complete Survey &amp;amp; Registration.]]></description>
			<restrictions><![CDATA[&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;THIS OFFER CANNOT BE INCENTIVIZED.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Search engine marketers are NOT permitted to bid on nor
utilize trademarked brand name keywords such as or any derivations thereof.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;No utilization of trademarked/branded terms in ad copy nor
purchasing such names in domains (i.e., etc.).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Trademarked/branded terms should be selected for Negative
match.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Landing/jump pages created should not resemble the
Advertiser's site(s) to give the impression it is the actual site.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Any violations will not be paid for and may result in
termination of your account.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The usage of Creative/texts (banners, e-mail, text ads etc)
that were not provided by the advertiser, will only be allowed upon the
advertiser's approval.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;This program is under budget; please contact your
affiliate manager to get more information.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;No VC, No Content Locking. Pop traffic must be approved.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 11px;"&gt;Valid Lead Criteria: 18+; completed survey / registration.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Traffic Accepted: US.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Distribution Methods Allowed: (Contextual / PPC), Display, Mobile Display&lt;/p&gt;]]></restrictions>
			<tc>
			</tc>
			<categories>eCommerce</categories>
			<mobile_tags>
			</mobile_tags>
			<countries> US</countries>
			<media_types>Display, Pops, Mobile Display</media_types>
			<languages>
			</languages>
			<tracking_duration>30</tracking_duration>
			<deep_links>0</deep_links>
			<date_created>2014-05-01 11:58:13</date_created>
			<date_updated>2014-05-29 19:18:27</date_updated>
		</program>
		<program>
			<id>127642</id>
			<name>FreeScoreConnect-US-Incent</name>
			<url>https://secure.rspcdn.com</url>
			<association_status>Approved</association_status>
			<logo>http://network.adsmarket.com/site/StoredImage?cid=3395da24</logo>
			<description><![CDATA[&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:8.5pt;font-family:Arial, sans-serif;"&gt;Offer Review:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:8.5pt;font-family:Arial, sans-serif;"&gt;&lt;br&gt;
Consumers can see their credit score for free and get their credit report for
$1.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;u&gt;Affiliate Benefits:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;
Optimized user-flow, higher conversion rate&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;u&gt;User Flow:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br&gt;
User must fill out the forms on the first and second page including social
security number and credit card information; pixel fires on &ldquo;continue to view
score&rdquo;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;u&gt;Typical Demographics:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;br&gt;
18+, US only and INCENT&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;]]></description>
			<restrictions><![CDATA[&lt;br&gt;&lt;p style="margin:0cm 0cm .0001pt 36pt;text-indent:-18pt;"&gt;Valid Lead Criteria - &lt;span style="font-size:8.5pt;font-family:Arial, sans-serif;"&gt;User must fill out the forms on the first and second page including social
security number and credit card information; pixel fires on &ldquo;continue to view
score&rdquo;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="margin:0cm 0cm .0001pt 36pt;text-indent:-18pt;"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:8.5pt;font-family:Arial, sans-serif;"&gt;All information must be VALID&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;]]></restrictions>
			<tc>
			</tc>
			<categories>Finance,Incentivized</categories>
			<mobile_tags>
			</mobile_tags>
			<countries> US</countries>
			<media_types>Display, Email, Pops</media_types>
			<languages> eng</languages>
			<tracking_duration>30</tracking_duration>
			<deep_links>0</deep_links>
			<date_created>2014-05-14 15:18:52</date_created>
			<date_updated>2014-08-01 11:25:44</date_updated>
		</program>
		<program>
			<id>127722</id>
			<name>LMB - Refinance - NON INCENT</name>
			<url>https://www.lowermybills.com/lending/home-refinance</url>
			<association_status>Approved</association_status>
			<logo>http://network.adsmarket.com/site/StoredImage?cid=33a474a8</logo>
			<description><![CDATA[Homeowners can compare refinance rates.&lt;br&gt;User Flow: &amp;nbsp;Registration.]]></description>
			<restrictions><![CDATA[Valid Lead Criteria: 18+; Registration page.]]></restrictions>
			<tc>
			</tc>
			<categories>Finance</categories>
			<mobile_tags>
			</mobile_tags>
			<countries> US</countries>
			<media_types>Display, Email, Pops</media_types>
			<languages>
			</languages>
			<tracking_duration>30</tracking_duration>
			<deep_links>0</deep_links>
			<date_created>2014-05-15 10:31:29</date_created>
			<date_updated>2014-08-01 11:29:14</date_updated>
		</program>
		<program>
			<id>129375</id>
			<name>The Unique Card - US - NON INCENT</name>
			<url>https://theuniquecard.com/</url>
			<association_status>Approved</association_status>
			<logo>http://network.adsmarket.com/site/StoredImage?cid=347c81eb</logo>
			<description><![CDATA[Consumers can get a $1000.00 credit line with instant approval.&lt;br&gt;User Flow: 1st page email submit.]]></description>
			<restrictions><![CDATA[Valid Lead Criteria: 18+; 1st page email submit.Traffic Accepted: US.&lt;br&gt;]]></restrictions>
			<tc>
			</tc>
			<categories>Finance</categories>
			<mobile_tags>
			</mobile_tags>
			<countries> US</countries>
			<media_types>Display, Email</media_types>
			<languages>
			</languages>
			<tracking_duration>30</tracking_duration>
			<deep_links>0</deep_links>
			<date_created>2014-05-29 13:39:34</date_created>
			<date_updated>2014-08-01 11:41:15</date_updated>
		</program>
		<program>
			<id>129735</id>
			<name>DaterSearch - Int' - Non Incent - Web</name>
			<url>matomy.com</url>
			<association_status>Approved</association_status>
			<logo>http://network.adsmarket.com/site/StoredImage?cid=34a1d3e7</logo>
			<description><![CDATA[Offer Review:&lt;br&gt;Find Fun, Love, or Friendship Today! Over 2,000,000 People&lt;br&gt;Have Used datersearch to Connect! Join Today!&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Affiliate Benefits:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;Higher rates available for high-performing affiliates, at the advertiser's discretion.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;User Flow:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;User must enter his/her Gender and Gender he/she is looking for, Name and Surname, ZIP postal, Valid&lt;br&gt;Email address and click to register. Conversion occurs upon email address verification, double opt in.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Typical Demographics:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;18+]]></description>
			<restrictions><![CDATA[Brand bidding is not allowed.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;Valid Conversion Criteria: &lt;br&gt;User must enter his/her Gender and Gender he/she is looking for, Name and Surname, ZIP postal,&lt;br&gt;Valid Email address and click to register. Conversion occurs upon email address verification, double opt in.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;]]></restrictions>
			<tc>
			</tc>
			<categories>Dating</categories>
			<mobile_tags>
			</mobile_tags>
			<countries> AU, CA, NZ, NO, GB, US</countries>
			<media_types>Display, Email, GDN, Pops, Search</media_types>
			<languages>
			</languages>
			<tracking_duration>45</tracking_duration>
			<deep_links>0</deep_links>
			<date_created>2014-06-03 05:44:04</date_created>
			<date_updated>2015-01-13 05:25:34</date_updated>
		</program>
		<program>
			<id>129745</id>
			<name>DaterSearch - Int' - Non Incent - Wap</name>
			<url><![CDATA[https://cpafund.offerit.com/track/MTQ0LjYzLjYzLjg0LjAuMC4wLjAuMC4wLjAuMA?_ocid=[CLICKIDN]&amp;subaff=[PUB_ID]&amp;subaff2=[PRG_ID]]]></url>
			<association_status>Approved</association_status>
			<logo>http://network.adsmarket.com/site/StoredImage?cid=34a3734b</logo>
			<description><![CDATA[Offer Review:&lt;br&gt;Find Fun, Love, or Friendship Today! Over 2,000,000 People&lt;br&gt;Have Used datersearch to Connect! Join Today!&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Affiliate Benefits:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;Higher rates available for high-performing affiliates, at the advertiser's discretion.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;User Flow:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;User must enter his/her Gender and Gender he/she is looking for, Name and Surname, ZIP postal, Valid&lt;br&gt;Email address and click to register. Conversion occurs upon email address verification, double opt in.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Typical Demographics:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;18+]]></description>
			<restrictions><![CDATA[Brand bidding is not allowed.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Valid Conversion Criteria: &lt;br&gt;User must enter his/her Gender and Gender he/she is looking for, Name and Surname, ZIP postal,&lt;br&gt;Valid Email address and click to register. Conversion occurs upon email address verification, double opt in.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;]]></restrictions>
			<tc>
			</tc>
			<categories>Mobile Optimized,Dating</categories>
			<mobile_tags>
			</mobile_tags>
			<countries> AU, CA, NZ, NO, GB, US</countries>
			<media_types>Display, GDN, In App, Mobile Display, Pops, Search</media_types>
			<languages>
			</languages>
			<tracking_duration>45</tracking_duration>
			<deep_links>0</deep_links>
			<date_created>2014-06-03 06:26:55</date_created>
			<date_updated>2014-11-03 09:16:05</date_updated>
		</program>
		<program>
			<id>130065</id>
			<name>Pearl's Peril - non incentivized - iPad</name>
			<url>https://itunes.apple.com/us/app/pearls-peril/id594802437?mt=8</url>
			<association_status>Approved</association_status>
			<logo>http://network.adsmarket.com/site/StoredImage?cid=3661abb7</logo>
			<description><![CDATA[Description
    
    
  
  
    Get swept back to the romantic 
and sordid 1930&rsquo;s along with our trailblazing heroine, Pearl Wallace, 
ace pilot and world explorer. Travel the world, uncover a global 
conspiracy, and navigate a chilling mystery you wont soon forget!&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Pearl&rsquo;s
 glamorous social life grinds to a halt when her father mysteriously 
dies and she inherits a wonderful island filled with perilous secrets. 
Journey with Pearl and her deliciously sarcastic best friend, Iris 
Hillman.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Talented enough to solve a mystery? Keen to find Hidden Objects? Love a great story?&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;User Flow: dowload - install - open app for the first time&lt;br&gt;]]></description>
			<restrictions><![CDATA[&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:9pt;"&gt;This offer is running under budget. Please contact your
AM if you wish to run it. &lt;br&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;Start new publishers with 70 installs/day until we get feedback&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;Traffic From designated geo&amp;nbsp; Only&lt;br&gt;No iPhone traffic, No iPod Traffic&lt;br&gt;No Virtual Currency Traffic &lt;br&gt;No Co-Registration Marketing &amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;No forced clicks&lt;br&gt;No automatic redirection to the appstore&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In order to run this offer with Adwords, please contact your account manager.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Valid Conversion Criteria: &lt;br&gt;User who installs the app and open it for the first time&lt;br&gt;]]></restrictions>
			<tc>
			</tc>
			<categories>Mobile Apps,Games</categories>
			<mobile_tags>iPad</mobile_tags>
			<countries> AU, CA, DE, GB, US</countries>
			<media_types>In App, Mobile Display, Search, Social</media_types>
			<languages> eng</languages>
			<tracking_duration>45</tracking_duration>
			<deep_links>0</deep_links>
			<date_created>2014-06-06 09:51:21</date_created>
			<date_updated>2014-12-01 03:33:13</date_updated>
		</program>
		<program>
			<id>131745</id>
			<name>Vittalia - Tiers - Non Incentivized - Semi Direct Download Links</name>
			<url>www.matomy.com</url>
			<association_status>Approved</association_status>
			<logo>http://network.adsmarket.com/site/StoredImage?cid=35ad8f5b</logo>
			<description><![CDATA[&lt;u&gt;&lt;b&gt;Publisher Rates:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;p style="text-align:left;"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;http://www.tsxnrey.com/i/Vittalia/Country%2016.7.14.pdf&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Offer Review:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;Popular downloads products for the everyday PC user including Media Players, Torrents, Codepacks, Antivirus and more!&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Affiliate Benefits:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;High-converting array of products available in a variety of hot countries. &lt;br&gt;Higher rates available for high-performing affiliates, at the advertiser's discretion.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;User Flow:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;User clicks to download, then installs product on their computer.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Typical Demographics:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;All&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;]]></description>
			<restrictions><![CDATA[&lt;u&gt;&lt;b&gt;Publisher Rates:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:'Segoe UI Symbol', 'sans-serif';color:#44546A;"&gt;Traffic Allowed from specific country only according to the attached link:&lt;br&gt;http://www.tsxnrey.com/i/Vittalia/Country%2016.7.14.pdf&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;No Incentivized Traffic&lt;br&gt;No Virtual Currency Traffic &lt;br&gt;No Co-Registration Marketing&amp;nbsp; &lt;br&gt;No Content Locking &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Valid Conversion Criteria: &lt;br&gt;User clicks to download, then installs product on their computer. Valid Conversion fires upon&lt;br&gt;successful installation, regardless of any bundled accepted along the installer path.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Creative Guidelines: &lt;br&gt;In addition to the creative materials supplied by Advertiser, Matomy and its Publishers may use&lt;br&gt;additional creative materials.&lt;br&gt;]]></restrictions>
			<tc>
			</tc>
			<categories>Downloads</categories>
			<mobile_tags>
			</mobile_tags>
			<countries> DZ, BE, BR, DK, EG, FI, FR, DE, IN, IQ, JP, JO, KW, NL, PK, PE, RU, SA, ES, SE, TH, TN, AE, GB, US, VE</countries>
			<media_types>Display, Pops</media_types>
			<languages>
			</languages>
			<tracking_duration>45</tracking_duration>
			<deep_links>0</deep_links>
			<date_created>2014-06-23 06:37:31</date_created>
			<date_updated>2015-02-11 03:50:53</date_updated>
		</program>
		<program>
			<id>132305</id>
			<name>Wamba  US Non Incent Web</name>
			<url><![CDATA[http://partner.wamba.com/link.phtml?pid=1275344462&amp;lid=34729]]></url>
			<association_status>Approved</association_status>
			<logo>http://network.adsmarket.com/site/StoredImage?cid=35f5c43d</logo>
			<description><![CDATA[Offer Review:&lt;br&gt;a Dating offer for US, Wamba is a global social networking service for meeting new people, the first Freemium social networking site in the world, now expanded to additional countries.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Affiliate Benefits:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;Higher rates available for high-performing affiliates, at the advertiser's discretion.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;User Flow:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;User signs in with his facebook account and then enters valid email, first name, gender, date of birth, gender seek, city and clicks submit. Double opt-in, email verification required.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Typical Demographics:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;Focus on females for best Advertiser quality assessment.&lt;br&gt;18+&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;]]></description>
			<restrictions><![CDATA[Valid Conversion Criteria: &lt;br&gt;User enters valid email, first name, gender, date of birth, gender seek, city and clicks submit. Double&lt;br&gt;opt-in, email verification required. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;this program is under budget please ask your account manager for allocation&lt;br&gt;]]></restrictions>
			<tc>
			</tc>
			<categories>Dating</categories>
			<mobile_tags>
			</mobile_tags>
			<countries> US</countries>
			<media_types>Display, Email, Pops, Social</media_types>
			<languages>
			</languages>
			<tracking_duration>30</tracking_duration>
			<deep_links>0</deep_links>
			<date_created>2014-06-25 02:06:41</date_created>
			<date_updated>2014-11-03 09:12:23</date_updated>
		</program>
		<program>
			<id>133515</id>
			<name>BeenVerfied - US - Non Incent</name>
			<url>http://www.beenverified.com/</url>
			<association_status>Approved</association_status>
			<logo>http://network.adsmarket.com/site/StoredImage?cid=36738503</logo>
			<description><![CDATA[Offer Review:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;BeenVerified&rsquo;s mission is to give people easy and affordable access to public record information.&lt;br&gt;Criminal Records, Bankruptcies, Contact Information, and More!&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Affiliate Benefits:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;Higher rates available for high-performing affiliates, at the advertiser's discretion.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;User Flow:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;User must enter his first name, last name and valid email address, choose a package, enter valid&lt;br&gt;payment details, agree to both check boxes and clicks "view report".&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Typical Demographics:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;ALL]]></description>
			<restrictions><![CDATA[Traffic Allowed from US Only&lt;br&gt;email traffic is to be run only from designated campaigns. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Search: Direct linking and Trademark bidding are strictly forbidden. The use of Jump pages is approved and should&lt;br&gt;include the BeenVerified Trademark/logo&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Valid Conversion Criteria: &lt;br&gt;User must enter his first name, last name and valid email address, choose a package, enter valid&lt;br&gt;payment details, agree to both check boxes and click "view report". At this point the conversion occurs, 100% of&lt;br&gt;conversions tracked by HasOffers and fired to Matomy will be approved.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Creative Restrictions:&lt;br&gt;Client has already approved the use of creative concepts previously submitted to him by Matomy,&lt;br&gt;pending the addition of "Beenverified" Trademark/logo. Any new creative concepts, must be approved by the advertiser. In&lt;br&gt;addition, the advertiser will provide Matomy with Advertiser's own creatives.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;]]></restrictions>
			<tc>
			</tc>
			<categories>Consumer Products</categories>
			<mobile_tags>
			</mobile_tags>
			<countries> US</countries>
			<media_types>Display, Email, GDN, Pops, Social</media_types>
			<languages> eng</languages>
			<tracking_duration>30</tracking_duration>
			<deep_links>0</deep_links>
			<date_created>2014-07-06 09:45:14</date_created>
			<date_updated>2014-12-02 12:50:10</date_updated>
		</program>
		<program>
			<id>135025</id>
			<name>GDCE- News Week Latino</name>
			<url>www.exur.com/int</url>
			<association_status>Approved</association_status>
			<description><![CDATA[&lt;p style="margin-bottom: 0.0001pt;"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 8.5pt; font-family: Arial, sans-serif;"&gt;Exur products gives you the opportunity to make money from your home.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="margin-bottom: 0.0001pt;"&gt;&lt;span lang="EN-US" style="font-size: 8.5pt; font-family: Arial, sans-serif;"&gt;Flow: The user only has to click in the banner, go to the landing page, fill 2 blanks and accept for the pixel to be fired.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="margin-bottom: 0.0001pt;"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family: Arial, sans-serif; font-size: 8.5pt;"&gt;Read Term and Conditions.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="margin-bottom: 0.0001pt;"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family: Arial, sans-serif; font-size: 8.5pt;"&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="margin-bottom: 0.0001pt;"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family: Arial, sans-serif; font-size: 8.5pt;"&gt;Los productos de Exur te dan la oportunidad de ganar dinero desde tu casa.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="margin-bottom: 0.0001pt;"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family: Arial, sans-serif; font-size: 8.5pt;"&gt;Flow: El usuario da click en la landing para llegar al registro, llena 2 campos y al llegar a la thank you page se dispara el pixel.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="margin-bottom: 0.0001pt;"&gt;Leer terminos y condiciones&lt;/p&gt;]]></description>
			<restrictions><![CDATA[&lt;p style="margin: 0px 0px 0.0001pt; padding: 0px; text-rendering: optimizelegibility; font-size: 11.333333015441895px; color: rgb(102, 102, 102);"&gt;&lt;span style="margin: 0px; padding: 0px; text-rendering: optimizelegibility; font-size: 8.5pt; font-family: Arial, sans-serif;"&gt;No se acepta Tr&aacute;fico Incentivado.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="margin: 0px 0px 0.0001pt; padding: 0px; text-rendering: optimizelegibility; font-size: 11.333333015441895px; color: rgb(102, 102, 102);"&gt;&lt;span style="margin: 0px; padding: 0px; text-rendering: optimizelegibility; font-size: 8.5pt; font-family: Arial, sans-serif;"&gt;No se acepta Virtual Currency.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="margin: 0px 0px 0.0001pt; padding: 0px; text-rendering: optimizelegibility; font-size: 11.333333015441895px; color: rgb(102, 102, 102);"&gt;&lt;span style="margin: 0px; padding: 0px; text-rendering: optimizelegibility; font-size: 8.5pt; font-family: Arial, sans-serif;"&gt;No se acepta Co-Registration.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="margin: 0px; padding: 0px; text-rendering: optimizelegibility; font-size: 11.333333015441895px; color: rgb(102, 102, 102);"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="margin: 0px 0px 0.0001pt; padding: 0px; text-rendering: optimizelegibility; font-size: 11.333333015441895px; color: rgb(102, 102, 102);"&gt;&lt;span style="margin: 0px; padding: 0px; text-rendering: optimizelegibility; font-size: 8.5pt; font-family: Arial, sans-serif;"&gt;No publicar en sitios para Adultos.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="margin: 0px; padding: 0px; text-rendering: optimizelegibility; font-size: 11.333333015441895px; color: rgb(102, 102, 102);"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="margin: 0px 0px 0.0001pt; padding: 0px; text-rendering: optimizelegibility; font-size: 11.333333015441895px; color: rgb(102, 102, 102);"&gt;&lt;br style="margin: 0px; padding: 0px; text-rendering: optimizelegibility;"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="margin: 0px 0px 0.0001pt; padding: 0px; text-rendering: optimizelegibility; font-size: 11.333333015441895px; color: rgb(102, 102, 102);"&gt;&lt;span lang="en-us" style="margin: 0px; padding: 0px; text-rendering: optimizelegibility; font-size: 8.5pt; font-family: Arial, sans-serif;"&gt;Incentivized traffic not allowed&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br style="margin: 0px; padding: 0px; text-rendering: optimizelegibility; font-size: 11.333333015441895px;"&gt;Virtual currency traffic not allowed&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="margin: 0px 0px 0.0001pt; padding: 0px; text-rendering: optimizelegibility; font-size: 11.333333015441895px; color: rgb(102, 102, 102);"&gt;&lt;span lang="en-us" style="margin: 0px; padding: 0px; text-rendering: optimizelegibility; font-size: 8.5pt; font-family: Arial, sans-serif;"&gt;Co-Registration not allowed&lt;/span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="margin: 0px 0px 0.0001pt; padding: 0px; text-rendering: optimizelegibility; font-size: 11.333333015441895px; color: rgb(102, 102, 102);"&gt;No Adult Sites.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="margin: 0px 0px 0.0001pt; padding: 0px; text-rendering: optimizelegibility; font-size: 11.333333015441895px; color: rgb(102, 102, 102);"&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="margin: 0px 0px 0.0001pt; padding: 0px; text-rendering: optimizelegibility; font-size: 11.333333015441895px; color: rgb(102, 102, 102);"&gt;This program will only accept traffic from the following countries:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="margin: 0px 0px 0.0001pt; padding: 0px; text-rendering: optimizelegibility; font-size: 11.333333015441895px; color: rgb(102, 102, 102);"&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="margin: 0px 0px 0.0001pt; padding: 0px; text-rendering: optimizelegibility; font-size: 11.333333015441895px; color: rgb(102, 102, 102);"&gt;- UNITED STATES, PUERTO RICO&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="margin: 0px 0px 0.0001pt; padding: 0px; text-rendering: optimizelegibility; font-size: 11.333333015441895px; color: rgb(102, 102, 102);"&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;]]></restrictions>
			<tc>
			</tc>
			<categories>Biz Op</categories>
			<mobile_tags>
			</mobile_tags>
			<countries> AX, AR, BO, CL, CO, CR, EC, SV, GT, HN, MX, NI, PA, PY, PE, PT, PR, ES, US, UY, VE</countries>
			<media_types>Content Locking, Display, In App, Mobile Display, Pops, Social</media_types>
			<languages> esp</languages>
			<tracking_duration>45</tracking_duration>
			<deep_links>0</deep_links>
			<date_created>2014-07-22 18:21:26</date_created>
			<date_updated>2015-01-29 16:08:25</date_updated>
		</program>
		<program>
			<id>135105</id>
			<name>NEW Rail Nation International Non Incentivized</name>
			<url>www.matomy.com</url>
			<association_status>Approved</association_status>
			<logo>http://network.adsmarket.com/site/StoredImage?cid=378b6be5</logo>
			<description><![CDATA[&lt;b&gt;Browser game&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/b&gt;Rail Nation combines an in-depth transport simulation with a refines strategy game in charming&lt;br&gt;graphics. As founder of a railroad company the user can turn a sleepy town with historical steam train into a vibrant metropolis with electric railways. It is the players goal to transport as many goods as possible through six historic railroad eras, to interact with other players and to built up their own railroad network. The player has the chance to be the most influential tycoon with the best strategy within the endgame.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;b&gt;User Flow:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DOI&lt;br&gt;1. The user starts in the www.rail-nation.com&lt;br&gt;home page and clicks on &ldquo;Register Now&rdquo;&lt;br&gt;button. After clicking on the button, the&lt;br&gt;system takes him/her to the registration&lt;br&gt;form.&lt;br&gt;2. In the registration form, the user enters a&lt;br&gt;player name, e-mail address and a&lt;br&gt;password. After clicking on the &ldquo;Register&rdquo; button, the&lt;br&gt;user is sent an activation e-mail.&lt;br&gt;3. When the user clicks on the link in the&lt;br&gt;activation e-mail, or fills in the activation&lt;br&gt;code on himself, he / she is sent to the&lt;br&gt;website and receives a message that the&lt;br&gt;activation was successful.&lt;br&gt;3.1. The partner tracking pixel is&lt;br&gt;triggered at the moment of&lt;br&gt;activation.&lt;br&gt;The relevant entry can be found in&lt;br&gt;the source code for the HTML&lt;br&gt;page.&lt;b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Target group:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;- Player type: casual and core games,&lt;br&gt;- Gender distribution: 10% female, 90% male,&lt;br&gt;- Age group: 24-50 years old,&lt;br&gt;- Genre:&lt;br&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Simulation/strategy&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;- Similar games:&lt;br&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Forge of Empires,&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Anno Online,&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Trainstation,&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Skyrama,&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;The Settlers Online,&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;- Literature &amp;amp; Films:&lt;br&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Around the world in 80 days,&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;The Time Machine,&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Back to the future series,&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;The talking of Pelham 1, 2, 3,&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;]]></description>
			<restrictions><![CDATA[&lt;span style="color:rgb(102,102,102);background-color:rgb(255,255,255);"&gt;Traffic only allowed from countries set as campaigns!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;Please note: publishers have to cap to 100&euro;/day/campaign&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;p style="margin:0px;padding:0px;color:rgb(102,102,102);"&gt;&lt;span style="margin:0px;padding:0px;background-color:rgb(255,255,255);"&gt;Only affiliates who agreed to Travian addendum can access the links!&amp;nbsp;Here's the link for the addendum -&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="margin:0px;padding:0px;color:rgb(102,102,102);"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="margin:0px;padding:0px;color:rgb(102,102,102);"&gt;&lt;span style="margin:0px;padding:0px;color:rgb(31,73,125);"&gt;http://mockup.tsxnrey.com/9096-Travian_publisher_addendum_20101015.DOC&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;Geo&acute;s and payout list:&lt;u&gt;http://www.tsxnrey.com/i/Sandra/Sandra/Rail%20Nation%20Int%c2%b4l_Updated%20Payouts.pdf&lt;/u&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;]]></restrictions>
			<tc>
			</tc>
			<categories>Games</categories>
			<mobile_tags>
			</mobile_tags>
			<countries> AR, AU, AT, BE, BR, CA, CZ, DK, FI, FR, DE, GR, IE, IL, IT, JP, NL, NO, PL, PT, RO, RU, ZA, ES, SE, CH, TR, UA, GB, US</countries>
			<media_types>Display, Pops</media_types>
			<languages>
			</languages>
			<tracking_duration>45</tracking_duration>
			<deep_links>0</deep_links>
			<date_created>2014-07-23 05:08:19</date_created>
			<date_updated>2015-01-12 04:51:00</date_updated>
		</program>
		<program>
			<id>135115</id>
			<name>NEW Travian 4 non incentivized</name>
			<url>www.matomy.com</url>
			<association_status>Approved</association_status>
			<logo>http://network.adsmarket.com/site/StoredImage?cid=3a86f1f4</logo>
			<description><![CDATA[&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight:bold;"&gt;Browser game&lt;br&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight:bold;"&gt;Travian 4:.&lt;/span&gt; The new version 
includes many fun new features! The artistic design is completely redone
 with extremely detailed and vivid graphics. The new design will not 
only reflect the exciting progress of the game, but also offer valuable 
information to the player.&lt;span style="font-size:10.5pt;font-family:Arial, 'sans-serif';color:rgb(51,51,51);"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:10.5pt;font-family:Arial, 'sans-serif';color:rgb(51,51,51);"&gt;
&lt;/span&gt;Travian is a browser game featuring a world with thousands of 
other real players. One begins the game acting as a chief of a tiny 
village and can wage wars or trade with neighbors.&amp;nbsp; The program is 
international and converts all over the world!&amp;nbsp; * No downloads 
necessary, and the game is directly playable.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight:bold;"&gt;Flow: &lt;/span&gt;DOI - verify email address&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight:bold;"&gt;Target group&lt;/span&gt;:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:9pt;font-family:Verdana, 'sans-serif';color:#5A5A5A;"&gt;Player type: Casual and core gamers&lt;br&gt;
Gender distribution: 30% female, 70% male&lt;br&gt;
Age group: 16 &ndash; 40&lt;br&gt;
Interests: Strategy games, Comics, Movie websites &lt;br&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;]]></description>
			<restrictions><![CDATA[&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:8.5pt;font-family:Arial, 'sans-serif';color:#666666;background:#FFFFFF;" lang="en-us"&gt;Traffic only allowed from
countries set as campaigns!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:8.5pt;font-family:Arial, sans-serif;" lang="en-us"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Arial, sans-serif;font-size:8.5pt;"&gt;Please note: publishers have to cap to
100&euro;/day/campaign&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:8.5pt;font-family:Arial, sans-serif;" lang="en-us"&gt;
&lt;span style="color:rgb(102,102,102);font-size:8.5pt;background-color:#FFFFFF;"&gt;Only affiliates who agreed to
Travian addendum can access the links!&amp;nbsp;Here's the link for the addendum -&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;







&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:8.5pt;font-family:Arial, 'sans-serif';color:#1F497D;" lang="en-us"&gt;http://mockup.tsxnrey.com/9096-Travian_publisher_addendum_20101015.DOC&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:8.5pt;font-family:Arial, 'sans-serif';color:#666666;" lang="en-us"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:8.5pt;font-family:Arial, 'sans-serif';color:#1F497D;" lang="en-us"&gt;Geo&acute;s and payout list:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;http://www.tsxnrey.com/i/Sandra/Sandra/Travian%20Int%c2%b4l_Updated%20Payouts.pdf&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;]]></restrictions>
			<tc>
			</tc>
			<categories>Games</categories>
			<mobile_tags>
			</mobile_tags>
			<countries> AR, AU, AT, BH, BY, BE, BA, BR, BG, CA, CL, HR, CZ, DK, EG, EE, FI, FR, DE, GR, HK, HU, ID, IQ, IE, IL, IT, JP, JO, KW, LV, LB, LY, LI, LT, LU, MY, MT, MX, NL, NZ, NO, OM, PS, PL, PT, QA, RO, RU, SA, SK, SI, ZA, ES, SE, CH, SY, TW, TH, TN, TR, UA, AE, GB, US, VN, YE</countries>
			<media_types>Display, Pops</media_types>
			<languages>
			</languages>
			<tracking_duration>45</tracking_duration>
			<deep_links>0</deep_links>
			<date_created>2014-07-23 05:26:52</date_created>
			<date_updated>2015-01-12 04:51:47</date_updated>
		</program>
		<program>
			<id>136275</id>
			<name>GDCE - Diario de la Mujer</name>
			<url>www.exur.com/int</url>
			<association_status>Approved</association_status>
			<description><![CDATA[&lt;p style="margin-bottom:.0001pt;"&gt;Exur products gives you the opportunity to make money from your home.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="margin-bottom:.0001pt;"&gt;Flow: The user only has to click in the banner, go to the landing page, fill 2 blanks and accept for the pixel to be fired.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="margin-bottom:.0001pt;"&gt;Read Term and Conditions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="margin-bottom:.0001pt;"&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="margin-bottom:.0001pt;"&gt;Los productos de Exur te dan la oportunidad de ganar dinero desde tu casa.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="margin-bottom:.0001pt;"&gt;Flow: El usuario da click en la landing para llegar al registro, llena 2 campos y al llegar a la thank you page se dispara el pixel.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="margin-bottom:.0001pt;"&gt;Leer terminos y condiciones&lt;/p&gt;]]></description>
			<restrictions><![CDATA[&lt;p style="margin: 0px 0px 0.0001pt; padding: 0px;"&gt;No se acepta Tr&aacute;fico Incentivado.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="margin: 0px 0px 0.0001pt; padding: 0px;"&gt;No se acepta Virtual Currency.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="margin: 0px 0px 0.0001pt; padding: 0px;"&gt;No se acepta Co-Registration.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="margin: 0px 0px 0.0001pt; padding: 0px;"&gt;No publicar en sitios para Adultos.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="margin: 0px 0px 0.0001pt; padding: 0px;"&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="margin: 0px 0px 0.0001pt; padding: 0px;"&gt;Incentivized traffic not allowed&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="margin: 0px 0px 0.0001pt; padding: 0px;"&gt;Virtual currency traffic not allowed&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="margin: 0px 0px 0.0001pt; padding: 0px;"&gt;Co-Registration not allowed&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="margin: 0px 0px 0.0001pt; padding: 0px;"&gt;No Adult Sites.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="margin: 0px 0px 0.0001pt; padding: 0px;"&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="margin:0cm;margin-bottom:.0001pt"&gt;&lt;span lang="EN-US" style="font-size:
8.5pt;font-family:&amp;quot;Arial&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;sans-serif&amp;quot;;color:#666666;mso-ansi-language:EN-US"&gt;This
program will only accept traffic from the following countries:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="margin: 0cm 0cm 0.0001pt; text-rendering: optimizelegibility;"&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgb(102, 102, 102); font-family: Arial, sans-serif; font-size: 8.5pt;"&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="margin: 0cm 0cm 0.0001pt; text-rendering: optimizelegibility;"&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgb(102, 102, 102); font-family: Arial, sans-serif; font-size: 8.5pt;"&gt;UNITED STATES &amp;amp; PUERTO RICO&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;]]></restrictions>
			<tc>
			</tc>
			<categories>Biz Op</categories>
			<mobile_tags>
			</mobile_tags>
			<countries> AX, AR, BO, CL, CO, CR, EC, SV, GT, HN, MX, NI, PA, PY, PE, PT, PR, ES, US, UY, VE</countries>
			<media_types>Content Locking, Display, In App, Mobile Display, Pops, Social</media_types>
			<languages> esp</languages>
			<tracking_duration>30</tracking_duration>
			<deep_links>0</deep_links>
			<date_created>2014-07-28 15:49:34</date_created>
			<date_updated>2015-01-29 16:09:00</date_updated>
		</program>
		<program>
			<id>136295</id>
			<name>GDCE - La Mirada</name>
			<url>www.exur.com/int</url>
			<association_status>Approved</association_status>
			<description><![CDATA[&lt;p style="margin-bottom:.0001pt;"&gt;Exur products gives you the opportunity to make money from your home.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="margin-bottom:.0001pt;"&gt;Flow: The user only has to click in the banner, go to the landing page, fill 2 blanks and accept for the pixel to be fired.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="margin-bottom:.0001pt;"&gt;Read Term and Conditions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="margin-bottom:.0001pt;"&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="margin-bottom:.0001pt;"&gt;Los productos de Exur te dan la oportunidad de ganar dinero desde tu casa.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="margin-bottom:.0001pt;"&gt;Flow: El usuario da click en la landing para llegar al registro, llena 2 campos y al llegar a la thank you page se dispara el pixel.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="margin-bottom:.0001pt;"&gt;Leer terminos y condiciones&lt;/p&gt;]]></description>
			<restrictions><![CDATA[&lt;p style="margin: 0px 0px 0.0001pt; padding: 0px;"&gt;No se acepta Tr&aacute;fico Incentivado.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="margin: 0px 0px 0.0001pt; padding: 0px;"&gt;No se acepta Virtual Currency.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="margin: 0px 0px 0.0001pt; padding: 0px;"&gt;No se acepta Co-Registration.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="margin: 0px 0px 0.0001pt; padding: 0px;"&gt;No publicar en sitios para Adultos.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="margin: 0px 0px 0.0001pt; padding: 0px;"&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="margin: 0px 0px 0.0001pt; padding: 0px;"&gt;Incentivized traffic not allowed&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="margin: 0px 0px 0.0001pt; padding: 0px;"&gt;Virtual currency traffic not allowed&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="margin: 0px 0px 0.0001pt; padding: 0px;"&gt;Co-Registration not allowed&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="margin: 0px 0px 0.0001pt; padding: 0px;"&gt;No Adult Sites.&lt;span style="color: rgb(102, 102, 102); font-size: 11.333333015441895px;"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="margin: 0px 0px 0.0001pt; padding: 0px;"&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgb(102, 102, 102); font-size: 11.333333015441895px;"&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="margin:0cm;margin-bottom:.0001pt"&gt;&lt;span lang="EN-US" style="font-size:
8.5pt;font-family:&amp;quot;Arial&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;sans-serif&amp;quot;;color:#666666;mso-ansi-language:EN-US"&gt;This
program will only accept traffic from the following countries:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="margin: 0cm 0cm 0.0001pt; text-rendering: optimizelegibility;"&gt;&lt;span lang="EN-US" style="font-size:8.5pt;font-family:&amp;quot;Arial&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;sans-serif&amp;quot;;
color:#666666;mso-ansi-language:EN-US"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="margin: 0cm 0cm 0.0001pt; text-rendering: optimizelegibility;"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:8.5pt;font-family:&amp;quot;Arial&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;sans-serif&amp;quot;;
color:#666666"&gt;UNITED STATES, PUERTO RICO&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="margin: 0cm 0cm 0.0001pt; text-rendering: optimizelegibility;"&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;]]></restrictions>
			<tc>
			</tc>
			<categories>Biz Op</categories>
			<mobile_tags>
			</mobile_tags>
			<countries> AX, AR, BO, CL, CO, CR, EC, SV, GT, HN, MX, NI, PA, PY, PE, PT, PR, ES, US, UY, VE</countries>
			<media_types>Content Locking, Display, In App, Mobile Display, Pops, Social</media_types>
			<languages> esp</languages>
			<tracking_duration>45</tracking_duration>
			<deep_links>0</deep_links>
			<date_created>2014-07-28 17:56:31</date_created>
			<date_updated>2015-01-29 16:09:29</date_updated>
		</program>
		<program>
			<id>136315</id>
			<name><![CDATA[OnePiece-Int&acute;l-Non Incent.]]></name>
			<url>www.matomy.com</url>
			<association_status>Approved</association_status>
			<logo>http://network.adsmarket.com/site/StoredImage?cid=42722a3b</logo>
			<description><![CDATA[&lt;b&gt;Browser game&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;span lang="EN-US" style="font-size:10.5pt;font-family:
&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,serif;mso-fareast-font-family:SimSun;mso-bidi-font-family:
SimSun;color:#474746;mso-font-kerning:0pt;mso-ansi-language:EN-US;mso-fareast-language:
ZH-CN;mso-bidi-language:AR-SA"&gt;&ldquo;OnePiece Online&rdquo; provides a brand new &ldquo;ARPG
Tower Defense&rdquo; gameplay mode. ARPG Tower Defense gameplay combines the
role-playing, real time battle of ARPG with the &ldquo;tower defense&rdquo; battle mode; it
combines both battle strategy and operation into one and improve upon it which
creates a &ldquo;double enjoyment&rdquo;. This brand new gameplay mode will not only
provide brand new gameplay experience for players but add in new wave of energy
to the browser game market.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Affiliate Benefits:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;Higher rates available for high-performing affiliates, at the advertiser's discretion.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;User Flow:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;1. User fills the first page details (username,email,password &amp;amp; confirm password)&lt;br&gt;2. user needs to complete the character creation&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Typical Demographics:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;ALL&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;]]></description>
			<restrictions><![CDATA[&lt;span style="font-size: 14.6666669845581px;"&gt;&lt;b&gt;This program is under budget. Please contact your AM if you are interested in running it.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;]]></restrictions>
			<tc>
			</tc>
			<categories>Games</categories>
			<mobile_tags>
			</mobile_tags>
			<countries> CA, FR, DE, GB, US</countries>
			<media_types>Display, Pops</media_types>
			<languages> eng</languages>
			<tracking_duration>45</tracking_duration>
			<deep_links>0</deep_links>
			<date_created>2014-07-29 02:31:34</date_created>
			<date_updated>2015-02-16 06:51:07</date_updated>
		</program>
		<program>
			<id>137175</id>
			<name>FunkPlay - Int' - Non Incentivized - OLFA - Music</name>
			<url>www.matomy.com</url>
			<association_status>Approved</association_status>
			<logo>http://network.adsmarket.com/site/StoredImage?cid=384127a5</logo>
			<description><![CDATA[Offer Review:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;Join hundreds of thousands of satisfied members of FunkPlay who became 
tired of searching for Songs online, and now enjoy the hottest new Songs
 and timeless classics on our site.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Affiliate Benefits:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;Higher rates available for high-performing affiliates, at the advertiser's discretion.Hot offer with incredible conversion rates, strong landing page and pre-lander design, with a wide spread of geo's internationally which can be found at the link below.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;User Flow:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;User registers with basic personal information to create a free account, then submits valid payment&lt;br&gt;details for a free trial membership period to the service. CPA conversion will fire once user submits valid payment details.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;b&gt;Publisher Payouts:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;http://www.tsxnrey.com/i/JMedia/ratepergeo&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Typical Demographics:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;All]]></description>
			<restrictions><![CDATA[&lt;b&gt;Publisher Payouts:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;http://www.tsxnrey.com/i/JMedia/ratepergeo&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Creative Guidelines: In addition to the materials supplied by Advertiser, Matomy and its publishers may use their own creative materials, including generic "Play Now" buttons and pre-landers instead of the "Step 0" page provided. In any event, all traffic must lead to/through the standard "Step 1" page provided by Advertiser.&lt;br&gt;]]></restrictions>
			<tc>
			</tc>
			<categories>Entertainment</categories>
			<mobile_tags>
			</mobile_tags>
			<countries> AX, AD, AU, AT, BE, CA, CL, CY, DK, FI, FR, DE, GI, GR, GG, HK, IS, IE, IM, IT, JM, JP, JE, KW, LU, MX, MC, NL, NZ, NO, PT, PR, SG, ES, SE, CH, TT, TR, AE, GB, US</countries>
			<media_types>Display, In App, Mobile Display, Pops</media_types>
			<languages>
			</languages>
			<tracking_duration>45</tracking_duration>
			<deep_links>0</deep_links>
			<date_created>2014-08-06 03:39:07</date_created>
			<date_updated>2014-11-03 09:00:31</date_updated>
		</program>
		<program>
			<id>137185</id>
			<name>FunkPlay - Int' - Non Incentivized - OLFA - Books</name>
			<url>www.matomy.com</url>
			<association_status>Approved</association_status>
			<logo>http://network.adsmarket.com/site/StoredImage?cid=3842c709</logo>
			<description><![CDATA[Offer Review:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;Join hundreds of thousands of satisfied members of FunkPlay who became 
tired of searching for Books, Magazines &amp;amp; Comics online, and now 
enjoy the hottest new Books, Magazines &amp;amp; Comics and timeless 
classics on our site.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Affiliate Benefits:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;Higher rates available for high-performing affiliates, at the advertiser's discretion.Hot offer with incredible conversion rates, strong landing page and pre-lander design, with a wide spread of geo's internationally which can be found at the link below.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;User Flow:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;User registers with basic personal information to create a free account, then submits valid payment&lt;br&gt;details for a free trial membership period to the service. CPA conversion will fire once user submits valid payment details.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;b&gt;Publisher Payouts:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;http://www.tsxnrey.com/i/JMedia/ratepergeo&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Typical Demographics:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;All]]></description>
			<restrictions><![CDATA[&lt;b&gt;Publisher Payouts:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;http://www.tsxnrey.com/i/JMedia/ratepergeo&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Creative Guidelines: In addition to the materials supplied by Advertiser, Matomy and its publishers may use their own creative materials, including generic "Play Now" buttons and pre-landers instead of the "Step 0" page provided. In any event, all traffic must lead to/through the standard "Step 1" page provided by Advertiser.&lt;br&gt;]]></restrictions>
			<tc>
			</tc>
			<categories>Entertainment</categories>
			<mobile_tags>
			</mobile_tags>
			<countries> AX, AD, AU, AT, BE, CA, CL, CY, DK, FI, FR, DE, GI, GR, GG, HK, IS, IE, IM, IT, JM, JP, JE, KW, LU, MX, MC, NL, NZ, NO, PT, PR, SG, ES, SE, CH, TT, TR, AE, GB, US</countries>
			<media_types>Display, In App, Mobile Display, Pops</media_types>
			<languages>
			</languages>
			<tracking_duration>45</tracking_duration>
			<deep_links>0</deep_links>
			<date_created>2014-08-06 03:41:25</date_created>
			<date_updated>2014-11-03 09:01:06</date_updated>
		</program>
		<program>
			<id>137195</id>
			<name>FunkPlay - Int' - Non Incentivized - OLFA - Games</name>
			<url>www.matomy.com</url>
			<association_status>Approved</association_status>
			<logo>http://network.adsmarket.com/site/StoredImage?cid=384396bb</logo>
			<description><![CDATA[Offer Review:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;Join hundreds of thousands of satisfied members who became tired of 
traditional computer games, and now play the hottest new games and 
classics on our site.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Affiliate Benefits:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;Higher rates available for high-performing affiliates, at the advertiser's discretion.Hot offer with incredible conversion rates, strong landing page and pre-lander design, with a wide spread of geo's internationally which can be found at the link below.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;User Flow:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;User registers with basic personal information to create a free account, then submits valid payment&lt;br&gt;details for a free trial membership period to the service. CPA conversion will fire once user submits valid payment details.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;b&gt;Publisher Payouts:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;http://www.tsxnrey.com/i/JMedia/ratepergeo&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Typical Demographics:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;All]]></description>
			<restrictions><![CDATA[&lt;b&gt;Publisher Payouts:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;http://www.tsxnrey.com/i/JMedia/ratepergeo&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Creative Guidelines: In addition to the materials supplied by Advertiser, Matomy and its publishers may use their own creative materials, including generic "Play Now" buttons and pre-landers instead of the "Step 0" page provided. In any event, all traffic must lead to/through the standard "Step 1" page provided by Advertiser.&lt;br&gt;]]></restrictions>
			<tc>
			</tc>
			<categories>Entertainment</categories>
			<mobile_tags>
			</mobile_tags>
			<countries> AX, AD, AU, AT, BE, CA, CL, CY, DK, FI, FR, DE, GI, GR, GG, HK, IS, IE, IM, IT, JM, JP, JE, KW, LU, MX, MC, NL, NZ, NO, PT, PR, SG, ES, SE, CH, TT, TR, AE, GB, US</countries>
			<media_types>Display, In App, Mobile Display, Pops</media_types>
			<languages>
			</languages>
			<tracking_duration>45</tracking_duration>
			<deep_links>0</deep_links>
			<date_created>2014-08-06 03:42:55</date_created>
			<date_updated>2014-11-03 09:01:29</date_updated>
		</program>
		<program>
			<id>139125</id>
			<name>Scorpio - US - Incentivized - OLFA - Pre-Landers</name>
			<url>www.matomy.com</url>
			<association_status>Approved</association_status>
			<logo>http://network.adsmarket.com/site/StoredImage?cid=3b50f616</logo>
			<description><![CDATA[Offer Review:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;A Lead Gen offer for US with many pages and offers.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Affiliate Benefits:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;Higher rates available for high-performing affiliates, at the advertiser's discretion.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;User Flow:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;User enters 3 yes/no questions and then submit his/her email address. At this point conversion occurs,&lt;br&gt;Single Opt In.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Typical Demographics:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;ALL&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;]]></description>
			<restrictions><![CDATA[Creative Guidelines:&lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;the words "free" and "win" are not allowed.]]></restrictions>
			<tc>
			</tc>
			<categories>Lead Generation,Mobile Optimized</categories>
			<mobile_tags>
			</mobile_tags>
			<countries> US</countries>
			<media_types>Content Locking, Display, Email, GDN, In App, Incentivized, Mobile Display, Pops, Search, Social</media_types>
			<languages>
			</languages>
			<tracking_duration>45</tracking_duration>
			<deep_links>0</deep_links>
			<date_created>2014-08-26 11:58:06</date_created>
			<date_updated>2014-09-07 05:24:42</date_updated>
		</program>
		<program>
			<id>139276</id>
			<name>Purifier (Mac only) - Intl' - Web - Non Incent</name>
			<url>www.purifier.com</url>
			<association_status>Approved</association_status>
			<logo>http://network.adsmarket.com/site/StoredImage?cid=3b73d8fc</logo>
			<description><![CDATA[&lt;u&gt;&lt;b&gt;Offer Review:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;br&gt;Purifiy is the easiest way to clean and accelerate your Mac. Get even better performance with just one app!&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;b&gt;User Flow:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;br&gt;User submits valid email, password and password confirmation. User then submits valid payment details&lt;br&gt;to sign up for a free trial. CPA conversion occurs once user submits valid payment details.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;b&gt;Typical Demographics:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;br&gt;All&lt;br&gt;]]></description>
			<restrictions><![CDATA[&lt;p&gt;New publishers are limited to a daily cap of 100 leads until given feedback&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mac traffic only&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;u&gt;Valid Conversion Criteria:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/p&gt;User submits valid email, password and password confirmation. User then submits valid payment details&lt;br&gt;to sign up for a free trial. CPA conversion occurs once user submits valid payment details.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Restricted Geos:&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 7.5pt; font-family: Helvetica, sans-serif;"&gt;IN, CN, ID, KZ, NG, PK, EG, MA, KW, FJ, BW, CW, TZ, MV, PE, GT, CO, MY, RU&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;]]></restrictions>
			<tc>
			</tc>
			<categories>Software,Entertainment</categories>
			<mobile_tags>
			</mobile_tags>
			<countries> AF, AX, AL, DZ, AS, AD, AO, AI, A1, AQ, AG, AR, AM, AW, AP, AU, AT, AZ, BS, BH, BD, BB, BY, BE, BZ, BJ, BM, BT, BO, BQ, BA, BV, BR, IO, BN, BG, BF, BI, KH, CM, CA, CV, KY, CF, TD, CL, CX, CC, KM, CG, CD, CK, CR, CI, HR, CU, CY, CZ, DK, DJ, DM, DO, TP, EC, SV, GQ, ER, EE, ET, EU, FK, FO, FI, FR, GF, PF, TF, GA, GM, GE, DE, GH, GI, GR, GL, GD, GP, GU, GG, GN, GW, GY, HT, HM, HN, HK, HU, IS, IR, IQ, IE, IM, IL, IT, JM, JP, JE, JO, KE, KI, KP, KR, KG, LA, LV, LB, LS, LR, LY, LI, LT, LU, MO, MK, MG, MW, ML, MT, MH, MQ, MR, MU, YT, MX, FM, MD, MC, MN, ME, MS, MZ, MM, NA, NR, NP, NL, AN, NC, NZ, NI, NE, NU, NF, MP, NO, OM, PW, PS, PA, PG, PY, PH, PN, PL, PT, PR, QA, RE, RO, RW, SH, KN, LC, MF, PM, VC, WS, SM, ST, A2, SA, SN, RS, SC, SL, SG, SK, SI, SB, SO, ZA, GS, ES, LK, SD, SR, SJ, SZ, SE, CH, SY, TW, TJ, TH, TL, TG, TK, TO, TT, TN, TR, TM, TC, TV, UG, UA, AE, GB, US, UM, UY, UZ, VU, VA, VE, VN, VG, VI, WF, EH, YE, ZM, ZW</countries>
			<media_types>Display, Pops</media_types>
			<languages>
			</languages>
			<tracking_duration>45</tracking_duration>
			<deep_links>0</deep_links>
			<date_created>2014-08-27 08:01:25</date_created>
			<date_updated>2015-03-05 08:38:53</date_updated>
		</program>
		<program>
			<id>139653</id>
			<name>PlatiniumPromotions - US - Non Incentivized - OLFA</name>
			<url>www.matomy.com</url>
			<association_status>Approved</association_status>
			<logo>http://network.adsmarket.com/site/StoredImage?cid=3afc5777</logo>
			<description><![CDATA[Offer Review:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;A lead Generation offer with many offers for US.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Affiliate Benefits:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;Higher rates available for high-performing affiliates, at the advertiser's discretion.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;User Flow:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;User submits valid email address and clicks on "Submit". At this point conversion occurs, Single Opt In.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Typical Demographics:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;ALL&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;]]></description>
			<restrictions><![CDATA[&lt;br&gt;]]></restrictions>
			<tc>
			</tc>
			<categories>Lead Generation,Mobile Optimized</categories>
			<mobile_tags>
			</mobile_tags>
			<countries> US</countries>
			<media_types>Display, Email, GDN, Mobile Display, Pops, Search, Social</media_types>
			<languages>
			</languages>
			<tracking_duration>45</tracking_duration>
			<deep_links>0</deep_links>
			<date_created>2014-08-31 04:40:39</date_created>
			<date_updated>2014-08-31 03:52:40</date_updated>
		</program>
		<program>
			<id>139663</id>
			<name>PlatiniumPromotions - US - Incentivized - OLFA</name>
			<url>www.matomy.com</url>
			<association_status>Approved</association_status>
			<logo>http://network.adsmarket.com/site/StoredImage?cid=3afdf6db</logo>
			<description><![CDATA[Offer Review:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;A lead Generation offer with many offers for US.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Affiliate Benefits:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;Higher rates available for high-performing affiliates, at the advertiser's discretion.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;User Flow:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;User submits valid email address and clicks on "Submit". At this point conversion occurs, Single Opt In.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Typical Demographics:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;ALL&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;]]></description>
			<restrictions><![CDATA[&lt;br&gt;]]></restrictions>
			<tc>
			</tc>
			<categories>Lead Generation,Incentivized</categories>
			<mobile_tags>
			</mobile_tags>
			<countries> US</countries>
			<media_types>Content Locking, Display, Email, GDN, Incentivized, Mobile Display, Pops, Search, Social</media_types>
			<languages>
			</languages>
			<tracking_duration>45</tracking_duration>
			<deep_links>0</deep_links>
			<date_created>2014-08-31 04:55:06</date_created>
			<date_updated>2014-08-31 03:55:53</date_updated>
		</program>
		<program>
			<id>139936</id>
			<name>MUClassic - Int' - Non Incentivized</name>
			<url>www.matomy.com</url>
			<association_status>Approved</association_status>
			<logo>http://network.adsmarket.com/site/StoredImage?cid=3b1dd948</logo>
			<description><![CDATA[&lt;b&gt;Browser game &lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MU Classic, an awesome action RPG webgame of the year! Pick up weapons to dragons! Join MU Classic,create your own legend!&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Affiliate Benefits:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;Higher rates available for high-performing affiliates, at the advertiser's discretion.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;User Flow:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;user enters email address and password&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Typical Demographics:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;ALL]]></description>
			<restrictions><![CDATA[No Adult Traffic&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;tier1 : CA GB AU NL BE SE DK FI CH NO GL DE FR&lt;br&gt;tier2 : NZ AT EE IS AD VI AG SG&lt;br&gt;tier3 : SA IT CZ GR IL LV JP SI IE CY MO AG AX TC NC RU RO AE&lt;br&gt;tier4 : TH MY KR HU LT SK HK HR BG ZA MT PR RE BY BH&amp;nbsp; CR MU TT JO EG MX AF BM NC MQ ES AP PT TR PL&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Don't run on these sites:&lt;br&gt;z6.com&lt;br&gt;ladygames.com&lt;br&gt;girl.me&lt;br&gt;3dgames.la&lt;br&gt;kiwzi.net&lt;br&gt;3dfreegames.me&lt;br&gt;gamebaby.com&lt;br&gt;manygames.com&lt;br&gt;racinggamer.com&lt;br&gt;girlgames.la&lt;br&gt;xoxokids.com&lt;br&gt;gamebaby.net&lt;br&gt;gamefree.la&lt;br&gt;games.la&lt;br&gt;ladygames.us&lt;br&gt;ladygames.la&lt;br&gt;bestgames.la&lt;br&gt;gamebaby.la&lt;br&gt;z6games.la&lt;br&gt;kiwzi.us&lt;br&gt;gameohyeah.com&lt;br&gt;manygames.me&lt;br&gt;gamefree.co&lt;br&gt;girlgame.la&lt;br&gt;somegames.me&lt;br&gt;somegames.org&lt;br&gt;funnygames.la&lt;br&gt;yoyogames4u.com&lt;br&gt;yoyogamesme.com&lt;br&gt;sportsgames8.com&lt;br&gt;gameomg.net&lt;br&gt;gamelucky.net&lt;br&gt;gamesocool.com&lt;br&gt;girlgame.me&lt;br&gt;racinggames.me&lt;br&gt;gogamesnow.com&lt;br&gt;yoyogames.me&lt;br&gt;somegames.co&lt;br&gt;cookinggames.me&lt;br&gt;puzzlegames.la&lt;br&gt;Gameomg.me&lt;br&gt;Gameflows.com&lt;br&gt;Gamesaints.com&lt;br&gt;animehere.com&lt;br&gt;wallpaperhere.com&lt;br&gt;mangafox.me&lt;br&gt;mangafox.mobi&lt;br&gt;mangahere.co&lt;br&gt;es.mangahere.co&lt;br&gt;mangatown.com&lt;br&gt;m.mangatown.com&lt;br&gt;orzzzz.com&lt;br&gt;funnymama.com&lt;br&gt;playhit.com&lt;br&gt;]]></restrictions>
			<tc>
			</tc>
			<categories>Games</categories>
			<mobile_tags>
			</mobile_tags>
			<countries> AF, AX, AD, AG, AP, AU, AT, BH, BY, BE, BM, BR, BG, CA, CR, HR, CY, CZ, DK, EG, EE, FI, FR, DE, GR, GL, HK, HU, IS, ID, IE, IL, IT, JP, JO, KR, LV, LT, MO, MY, MT, MQ, MU, MX, NL, NC, NZ, NO, PH, PL, PT, PR, RE, RO, RU, SA, SG, SK, SI, ZA, ES, SE, CH, TH, TT, TR, TC, AE, GB, US, VI</countries>
			<media_types>Display, Email, GDN, Pops, Search, Social</media_types>
			<languages>
			</languages>
			<tracking_duration>30</tracking_duration>
			<deep_links>0</deep_links>
			<date_created>2014-09-03 07:09:14</date_created>
			<date_updated>2015-03-07 15:30:02</date_updated>
		</program>
		<program>
			<id>140466</id>
			<name>Scorpio - US - Incentivized - OLFA - Direct</name>
			<url>www.matomy.com</url>
			<association_status>Approved</association_status>
			<logo>http://network.adsmarket.com/site/StoredImage?cid=3b52957a</logo>
			<description><![CDATA[Offer Review:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;A Lead Gen offer for US with many pages and offers.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Affiliate Benefits:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;Higher rates available for high-performing affiliates, at the advertiser's discretion.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;User Flow:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;User enters 3 yes/no questions and then submit his/her email address. At this point conversion occurs,&lt;br&gt;Single Opt In.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Typical Demographics:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;ALL&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;]]></description>
			<restrictions><![CDATA[Creative Guidelines:&lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;the words "free" and "win" are not allowed.]]></restrictions>
			<tc>
			</tc>
			<categories>Lead Generation,Mobile Optimized</categories>
			<mobile_tags>
			</mobile_tags>
			<countries> US</countries>
			<media_types>Content Locking, Display, Email, GDN, In App, Incentivized, Mobile Display, Pops, Search, Social</media_types>
			<languages>
			</languages>
			<tracking_duration>45</tracking_duration>
			<deep_links>0</deep_links>
			<date_created>2014-09-07 06:25:49</date_created>
			<date_updated>2014-09-07 08:38:00</date_updated>
		</program>
		<program>
			<id>141616</id>
			<name>US NG Tech Support Pay Per Call</name>
			<url>www.nourl.com</url>
			<association_status>Approved</association_status>
			<description>tech</description>
			<restrictions>
			</restrictions>
			<tc>
			</tc>
			<categories>Pay Per Call</categories>
			<mobile_tags>
			</mobile_tags>
			<countries> US</countries>
			<media_types>Pops</media_types>
			<languages>
			</languages>
			<tracking_duration>45</tracking_duration>
			<deep_links>0</deep_links>
			<date_created>2014-09-19 18:27:58</date_created>
			<date_updated>2015-01-19 12:45:25</date_updated>
		</program>
		<program>
			<id>142056</id>
			<name>Tribal Wars 2 - Non Incent</name>
			<url>http://www.matomy.com/</url>
			<association_status>Approved</association_status>
			<logo>http://network.adsmarket.com/site/StoredImage?cid=3c1fd864</logo>
			<description><![CDATA[&lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:8.5pt;font-family:Arial, sans-serif;"&gt;Browser game&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;p&gt;The free online strategy game Tribal Wars 2 is set in a
medieval universe, filled with knights, generals and political decisions.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;
A medieval Massive Multiplayer Online (MMO) war game with a focus on battle
strategy and castle management.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;Tribal Wars 2 is the&amp;nbsp;Sequel of strategy-classic &ldquo;Tribal Wars&rdquo;&lt;br&gt;&lt;span style="color:rgb(102,102,102);background-color:rgb(255,255,255);"&gt;User Flow:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;User must input username, password, valid email, checkbox for terms &amp;amp; conditions, and click play.&amp;nbsp; first page submit SOI&lt;/span&gt;.]]></description>
			<restrictions><![CDATA[&lt;span style="font-weight:bold;"&gt;** This program is live under budget, please contact your account manager.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight:bold;"&gt;Publishers who can send sub_id's, please send via DP.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight:bold;"&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight:bold;"&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="color:rgb(102,102,102);background-color:rgb(255,255,255);"&gt;This program is live under 70 leads per publisher per day for the first month,&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;until quality feedback.&lt;br style="margin:0px;padding:0px;color:rgb(102,102,102);"&gt;&lt;span style="color:rgb(102,102,102);background-color:rgb(255,255,255);"&gt;traffic according to campaign country&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br style="margin:0px;padding:0px;color:rgb(102,102,102);"&gt;&lt;br style="margin:0px;padding:0px;color:rgb(102,102,102);"&gt;&lt;span style="color:rgb(102,102,102);background-color:rgb(255,255,255);"&gt;Banners inside facebook Apps may be placed by the Advertising Party if agreed upon in writing by InnoGames. NO AUTOMATIC ENTRY SERVICES &ndash; NO TRAFFIC FROM ILLEGAL SITES &ndash; (e.g. filesharing, pirate sites, &hellip;) NO TRAFFIC FROM INAPPROPRIATE SITES FOR USERS&lt;/span&gt;]]></restrictions>
			<tc>
			</tc>
			<categories>Games</categories>
			<mobile_tags>
			</mobile_tags>
			<countries> AR, AT, BR, CZ, DK, FI, FR, DE, GR, HU, IT, NL, NO, PL, PT, RO, RU, SK, ES, SE, CH, GB, US</countries>
			<media_types>Display</media_types>
			<languages>
			</languages>
			<tracking_duration>45</tracking_duration>
			<deep_links>0</deep_links>
			<date_created>2014-09-24 05:59:36</date_created>
			<date_updated>2015-01-12 04:27:50</date_updated>
		</program>
		<program>
			<id>142176</id>
			<name>RealPlayer-INTL-OLFA-Non Incent</name>
			<url>www.matomy.com</url>
			<association_status>Approved</association_status>
			<logo>http://network.adsmarket.com/site/StoredImage?cid=3c4d4754</logo>
			<description><![CDATA[Offer Review:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;Download videos 3X faster from video websites&lt;br&gt;Watch your PC videos on your TV wirelessly&lt;br&gt;Access to all RealPlayer Cloud premium features - $50 value&lt;br&gt;+100GB of personal video cloud storage&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Affiliate Benefits:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;Higher rates available for high-performing affiliates, at the advertiser's discretion.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;User Flow:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;1. User gets to the sign up page.&lt;br&gt;2. User needs to create an account (First name, Last name, Email, Password and accept t&amp;amp;c)&lt;br&gt;3. User needs to enter his payments details.&lt;br&gt;4. User confirms the $1.99 payment for the service.&lt;br&gt;5. The user is subscribed and the conversion occurs.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Typical Demographics:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;ALL]]></description>
			<restrictions><![CDATA[OLFA offer - web&amp;amp;mobile traffic from same link.&lt;br&gt;traffic from WW is accepted excluding Russia. &lt;br&gt;GDN/SEM:&lt;br&gt;In order to run this offer with Adwords, please contact your account manager&lt;br&gt;]]></restrictions>
			<tc>
			</tc>
			<categories>Mobile Optimized,Consumer Products</categories>
			<mobile_tags>
			</mobile_tags>
			<countries> AF, AX, AL, DZ, AS, AD, AO, AI, A1, AQ, AG, AR, AM, AW, AP, AU, AT, AZ, BS, BH, BD, BB, BY, BE, BZ, BJ, BM, BT, BO, BQ, BA, BW, BV, BR, IO, BN, BG, BF, BI, KH, CM, CA, CV, KY, CF, TD, CL, CN, CX, CC, CO, KM, CG, CD, CK, CR, CI, HR, CU, CW, CY, CZ, DK, DJ, DM, DO, TP, EC, EG, SV, GQ, ER, EE, ET, EU, FK, FO, FJ, FI, FR, GF, PF, TF, GA, GM, GE, DE, GH, GI, GR, GL, GD, GP, GU, GT, GG, GN, GW, GY, HT, HM, HN, HK, HU, IS, IN, ID, IR, IQ, IE, IM, IL, IT, JM, JP, JE, JO, KZ, KE, KI, KP, KR, KW, KG, LA, LV, LB, LS, LR, LY, LI, LT, LU, MO, MK, MG, MW, MY, MV, ML, MT, MH, MQ, MR, MU, YT, MX, FM, MD, MC, MN, ME, MS, MA, MZ, MM, NA, NR, NP, NL, AN, NC, NZ, NI, NE, NG, NU, NF, MP, NO, OM, PK, PW, PS, PA, PG, PY, PE, PH, PN, PL, PT, PR, QA, RE, RO, RW, SH, KN, LC, MF, PM, VC, WS, SM, ST, A2, SA, SN, RS, SC, SL, SG, SK, SI, SB, SO, ZA, GS, ES, LK, SD, SR, SJ, SZ, SE, CH, SY, TW, TJ, TZ, TH, TL, TG, TK, TO, TT, TN, TR, TM, TC, TV, UG, UA, AE, GB, US, UM, UY, UZ, VU, VA, VE, VN, VG, VI, WF, EH, YE, ZM, ZW</countries>
			<media_types>Display, GDN, In App, Mobile Display, Pops, Search, Social</media_types>
			<languages>
			</languages>
			<tracking_duration>45</tracking_duration>
			<deep_links>0</deep_links>
			<date_created>2014-09-28 02:55:35</date_created>
			<date_updated>2015-02-16 07:20:36</date_updated>
		</program>
		<program>
			<id>142186</id>
			<name>RealPlayer-INTL-OLFA-Incent</name>
			<url>www.matomy.com</url>
			<association_status>Approved</association_status>
			<logo>http://network.adsmarket.com/site/StoredImage?cid=3c4ee6b8</logo>
			<description><![CDATA[Offer Review:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;Download videos 3X faster from video websites&lt;br&gt;Watch your PC videos on your TV wirelessly&lt;br&gt;Access to all RealPlayer Cloud premium features - $50 value&lt;br&gt;+100GB of personal video cloud storage&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Affiliate Benefits:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;Higher rates available for high-performing affiliates, at the advertiser's discretion.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;User Flow:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;1. User gets to the sign up page.&lt;br&gt;2. User needs to create an account (First name, Last name, Email, Password and accept t&amp;amp;c)&lt;br&gt;3. User needs to enter his payments details.&lt;br&gt;4. User confirms the $1.99 payment for the service.&lt;br&gt;5. The user is subscribed and the conversion occurs.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Typical Demographics:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;ALL]]></description>
			<restrictions><![CDATA[OLFA offer - web&amp;amp;mobile traffic from same link.&lt;br&gt;traffic from WW is accepted excluding Russia. &lt;br&gt;GDN/SEM:&lt;br&gt;In order to run this offer with Adwords, please contact your account manager&lt;br&gt;]]></restrictions>
			<tc>
			</tc>
			<categories>Consumer Products,Incentivized,Mobile Optimized</categories>
			<mobile_tags>
			</mobile_tags>
			<countries> AF, AX, AL, DZ, AS, AD, AO, AI, A1, AQ, AG, AR, AM, AW, AP, AU, AT, AZ, BS, BH, BD, BB, BY, BE, BZ, BJ, BM, BT, BO, BQ, BA, BW, BV, BR, IO, BN, BG, BF, BI, KH, CM, CA, CV, KY, CF, TD, CL, CN, CX, CC, CO, KM, CG, CD, CK, CR, CI, HR, CU, CW, CY, CZ, DK, DJ, DM, DO, TP, EC, EG, SV, GQ, ER, EE, ET, EU, FK, FO, FJ, FI, FR, GF, PF, TF, GA, GM, GE, DE, GH, GI, GR, GL, GD, GP, GU, GT, GG, GN, GW, GY, HT, HM, HN, HK, HU, IS, IN, ID, IR, IQ, IE, IM, IL, IT, JM, JP, JE, JO, KZ, KE, KI, KP, KR, KW, KG, LA, LV, LB, LS, LR, LY, LI, LT, LU, MO, MK, MG, MW, MY, MV, ML, MT, MH, MQ, MR, MU, YT, MX, FM, MD, MC, MN, ME, MS, MA, MZ, MM, NA, NR, NP, NL, AN, NC, NZ, NI, NE, NG, NU, NF, MP, NO, OM, PK, PW, PS, PA, PG, PY, PE, PH, PN, PL, PT, PR, QA, RE, RO, RW, SH, KN, LC, MF, PM, VC, WS, SM, ST, A2, SA, SN, RS, SC, SL, SG, SK, SI, SB, SO, ZA, GS, ES, LK, SD, SR, SJ, SZ, SE, CH, SY, TW, TJ, TZ, TH, TL, TG, TK, TO, TT, TN, TR, TM, TC, TV, UG, UA, AE, GB, US, UM, UY, UZ, VU, VA, VE, VN, VG, VI, WF, EH, YE, ZM, ZW</countries>
			<media_types>Content Locking, Display, GDN, In App, Incentivized, Mobile Display, Pops, Search, Social</media_types>
			<languages>
			</languages>
			<tracking_duration>45</tracking_duration>
			<deep_links>0</deep_links>
			<date_created>2014-09-28 02:56:45</date_created>
			<date_updated>2015-02-16 07:22:35</date_updated>
		</program>
		<program>
			<id>142276</id>
			<name>Quizyourself - Pixel - Default</name>
			<url>www.matomy.com</url>
			<association_status>Approved</association_status>
			<description>jhkhjkhgkghkgk</description>
			<restrictions><![CDATA[&lt;br&gt;]]></restrictions>
			<tc>
			</tc>
			<categories>Surveys</categories>
			<mobile_tags>
			</mobile_tags>
			<countries> AF, AX, AL, DZ, AS, AD, AO, AI, A1, AQ, AG, AR, AM, AW, AP, AU, AT, AZ, BS, BH, BD, BB, BY, BE, BZ, BJ, BM, BT, BO, BQ, BA, BW, BV, BR, IO, BN, BG, BF, BI, KH, CM, CA, CV, KY, CF, TD, CL, CX, CC, CO, KM, CG, CD, CK, CR, CI, HR, CU, CW, CY, CZ, DK, DJ, DM, DO, TP, EC, EG, SV, GQ, ER, EE, ET, EU, FK, FO, FJ, FI, FR, GF, PF, TF, GA, GM, GE, DE, GH, GI, GR, GL, GD, GP, GU, GT, GG, GN, GW, GY, HT, HM, HN, HK, HU, IS, IN, ID, IR, IQ, IE, IM, IL, IT, JM, JP, JE, JO, KZ, KE, KI, KP, KR, KW, KG, LA, LV, LB, LS, LR, LY, LI, LT, LU, MO, MK, MG, MW, MY, MV, ML, MT, MH, MQ, MR, MU, YT, MX, FM, MD, MC, MN, ME, MS, MA, MZ, MM, NA, NR, NP, NL, AN, NC, NZ, NI, NE, NG, NU, NF, MP, NO, OM, PK, PW, PS, PA, PG, PY, PE, PH, PN, PL, PT, PR, QA, RE, RO, RU, RW, SH, KN, LC, MF, PM, VC, WS, SM, ST, A2, SA, SN, RS, SC, SL, SG, SK, SI, SB, SO, ZA, GS, ES, LK, SD, SR, SJ, SZ, SE, CH, SY, TW, TJ, TZ, TH, TL, TG, TK, TO, TT, TN, TR, TM, TC, TV, UG, UA, AE, GB, US, UM, UY, UZ, VU, VA, VE, VN, VG, VI, WF, EH, YE, ZM, ZW</countries>
			<media_types>Display</media_types>
			<languages>
			</languages>
			<tracking_duration>45</tracking_duration>
			<deep_links>0</deep_links>
			<date_created>2014-09-28 08:14:54</date_created>
			<date_updated>2014-09-28 07:16:07</date_updated>
		</program>
		<program>
			<id>142693</id>
			<name>Binary Profits - Intl' - Non Incent</name>
			<url>www.matomy.com</url>
			<association_status>Approved</association_status>
			<logo>http://network.adsmarket.com/site/StoredImage?cid=3cb820cd</logo>
			<description><![CDATA[AutoBinaryProfits is the first Binary offer built specifically for media! Profit from a full integrated checkout process and the highest CPA for a $10 deposit - the lowest deposit in the binary niche!&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:9pt;font-family:Arial, 'sans-serif';"&gt;Affiliate Benefits:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;span style="font-size:9pt;font-family:Arial, 'sans-serif';"&gt;GEO Targeted PRO
Written Sales Pages, Eye Catching Design, Fast Checkout Pages with Low Price
Points Means You Can Expect Super High Conversions and Higher Than Average
EPC's. Higher CPA Rates Available For High Performing Affiliates At Advertisers
Discretion.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/span&gt;user flow: &lt;span style="font-size:9pt;font-family:Arial, sans-serif;"&gt;1st Page: enters full name, a valid email address, phone number, country and
clicks 'Continue'.&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;
2nd page: user clicks "continue"&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;
3rd page: user enters personal and credit card information and clicks
"order now".&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Brand Bidding is allowed&lt;span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;]]></description>
			<restrictions><![CDATA[publishers need to run with a daily cap of $250-$300 at the first days]]></restrictions>
			<tc>
			</tc>
			<categories>Biz Op</categories>
			<mobile_tags>
			</mobile_tags>
			<countries> AU, AT, BE, BG, CA, HR, CY, CZ, DK, EE, FI, FR, DE, GR, HU, IE, IT, LV, LT, LU, MT, NL, PL, PT, RO, SG, SK, SI, ES, SE, AE, GB, US</countries>
			<media_types>Display, Email, GDN, Pops, Search, Social</media_types>
			<languages>
			</languages>
			<tracking_duration>45</tracking_duration>
			<deep_links>0</deep_links>
			<date_created>2014-10-01 08:55:04</date_created>
			<date_updated>2015-01-11 11:01:29</date_updated>
		</program>
		<program>
			<id>144573</id>
			<name>GetStudentLoanHelp - Pay Per Call- Pixel Tracking</name>
			<url><![CDATA[http://www.getstudentloanhelp.info/consolidate/suppget.php?&amp;transaction_id=&amp;affiliate_id=[PUB_ID]&amp;click_id=[CLICKIDN]&amp;billable=[DP]]]></url>
			<association_status>Approved</association_status>
			<description>Student Loan Relief PPC</description>
			<restrictions>
			</restrictions>
			<tc>
			</tc>
			<categories>Pay Per Call</categories>
			<mobile_tags>
			</mobile_tags>
			<countries> US</countries>
			<media_types>Display, Email, Mobile Display, Search, Social</media_types>
			<languages> eng</languages>
			<tracking_duration>30</tracking_duration>
			<deep_links>0</deep_links>
			<date_created>2014-10-23 20:26:58</date_created>
			<date_updated>2014-10-27 16:25:40</date_updated>
		</program>
		<program>
			<id>144724</id>
			<name>RussiaWomenDate - Intl' - Non Incentivized - Web</name>
			<url>www.matomy.com</url>
			<association_status>Approved</association_status>
			<logo>http://network.adsmarket.com/site/StoredImage?cid=413dde03</logo>
			<description><![CDATA[Offer Review:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;Fall in love in 2 mins' speed chat!&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Affiliate Benefits:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;Higher rates available for high-performing affiliates, at the advertiser's discretion.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;User Flow:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;On 1st page user submits valid gender &amp;amp; gender sought, name, last name, email address, password and&lt;br&gt;clicks on "Join now". On 2nd page user submits birthday, nationality, city of residence and clicks on "next". On 3rd page,&lt;br&gt;user submits "relationship status", "have a children?", "Height", "Weight" and "ideal match's age". At this point user clicks&lt;br&gt;on "Find my match" and pixel fires for all male 25+. Single opt-in, no email verification required.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Typical Demographics:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;ALL&lt;br&gt;]]></description>
			<restrictions><![CDATA[Adult, Torrent traffic, sexually wording is disallowed.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;the conversion will fire for male 25+.ONLY&lt;br&gt;Each campaign is for a different traffic source(display/email/pops)&lt;br&gt;Program&amp;nbsp; under budget please your account manager for allocation&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;If you are going to drop an e mail please contact your affiliate manager as we need to add your parameter.&lt;br&gt;]]></restrictions>
			<tc>
			</tc>
			<categories>Dating</categories>
			<mobile_tags>
			</mobile_tags>
			<countries> AU, CA, FI, IE, NZ, NO, SE, CH, GB, US</countries>
			<media_types>Display, Email, Pops</media_types>
			<languages>
			</languages>
			<tracking_duration>45</tracking_duration>
			<deep_links>0</deep_links>
			<date_created>2014-10-26 04:18:46</date_created>
			<date_updated>2015-03-08 06:50:02</date_updated>
		</program>
		<program>
			<id>145313</id>
			<name>FBFreebies - US - Incentivized - OLFA - Exclusive</name>
			<url>www.matomy.com</url>
			<association_status>Approved</association_status>
			<logo>http://network.adsmarket.com/site/StoredImage?cid=3deb9d53</logo>
			<description><![CDATA[Offer Review:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;A free stuff offer for US with mobile-optimized page.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Affiliate Benefits:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;Higher rates available for high-performing affiliates, at the advertiser's discretion.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;User Flow:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;User completes the flow on the pre-lander survey, Then the user submits his email, then complete the&lt;br&gt;lead form and the pixel fires.. Conversion occurs upon completing the survey and the second page details.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Typical Demographics:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;ALL&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;]]></description>
			<restrictions><![CDATA[&lt;br&gt;]]></restrictions>
			<tc>
			</tc>
			<categories>Lead Generation</categories>
			<mobile_tags>
			</mobile_tags>
			<countries> US</countries>
			<media_types>Content Locking, Display, Email, GDN, In App, Incentivized, Mobile Display, Pops</media_types>
			<languages>
			</languages>
			<tracking_duration>45</tracking_duration>
			<deep_links>0</deep_links>
			<date_created>2014-10-29 05:39:48</date_created>
			<date_updated>2014-10-30 04:53:57</date_updated>
		</program>
		<program>
			<id>147873</id>
			<name>RedLP- intl' -Non Incent-MAC</name>
			<url><![CDATA[http://macmtmy.com/mac/m1?dp=1&amp;cid=[CLICKIDN]]]></url>
			<association_status>Approved</association_status>
			<logo>http://network.adsmarket.com/site/StoredImage?cid=3f6e9bfd</logo>
			<description><![CDATA[Offer Review:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;A download offer for US/CA/UK/DE/FR/AU with Media Player HD installation.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Affiliate Benefits:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;Higher rates available for high-performing affiliates, at the advertiser's discretion.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;User Flow:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;User arrives on landing page, clicks to download then runs and installs product. Conversion will fire once&amp;nbsp;a user downloads and successfully installs products onto his computer.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Typical Demographics:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;ALL&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;]]></description>
			<restrictions><![CDATA[Operating System: MacManual approval by the affiliate manager is required.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Publisher Payouts:&lt;br&gt;US - $1.38&lt;br&gt;CA - $0.65&lt;br&gt;GB - $0.69&lt;br&gt;DE - $0.54&lt;br&gt;FR - $0.62&lt;br&gt;AU - $0.84&lt;br&gt;IT - $0.62&lt;br&gt;AT - $0.46&lt;br&gt;DK - $0.23&lt;br&gt;NL - $0.38&lt;br&gt;PT - $0.23&lt;br&gt;SE - $0.38&lt;br&gt;BR - $0.19&lt;br&gt;MX - $0.17&lt;br&gt;IN - $0.05&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;]]></restrictions>
			<tc>
			</tc>
			<categories>Downloads</categories>
			<mobile_tags>
			</mobile_tags>
			<countries> AU, AT, BR, CA, DK, FR, DE, IN, IT, MX, NL, PT, SE, GB, US</countries>
			<media_types>Display, Pops</media_types>
			<languages>
			</languages>
			<tracking_duration>45</tracking_duration>
			<deep_links>0</deep_links>
			<date_created>2014-11-23 10:40:23</date_created>
			<date_updated>2015-02-15 06:19:42</date_updated>
		</program>
		<program>
			<id>147883</id>
			<name>BlueLP- intl' -Non Incent-MAC</name>
			<url><![CDATA[http://macmtmy.com/mac/m2?dp=1&amp;cid=[CLICKIDN]]]></url>
			<association_status>Approved</association_status>
			<logo>http://network.adsmarket.com/site/StoredImage?cid=3f703b61</logo>
			<description><![CDATA[Offer Review:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;A download offer for US/CA/UK/DE/FR/AU with Media Player HD installation.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Affiliate Benefits:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;Higher rates available for high-performing affiliates, at the advertiser's discretion.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;User Flow:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;User arrives on landing page, clicks to download then runs and installs product. Conversion will fire once&lt;br&gt;a user downloads and successfully installs products onto his computer.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Typical Demographics:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;ALL&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;]]></description>
			<restrictions><![CDATA[Operating System: Mac&lt;span style="color:rgb(102,102,102);background-color:rgb(255,255,255);"&gt;Manual approval by the affiliate manager is required.&lt;br&gt;US - $1.38&lt;br&gt;CA - $0.65&lt;br&gt;GB - $0.69&lt;br&gt;DE - $0.54&lt;br&gt;FR - $0.62&lt;br&gt;AU - $0.84&lt;br&gt;IT - $0.62&lt;br&gt;AT - $0.46&lt;br&gt;DK - $0.23&lt;br&gt;NL - $0.38&lt;br&gt;PT - $0.23&lt;br&gt;SE - $0.38&lt;br&gt;BR - $0.19&lt;br&gt;MX - $0.17&lt;br&gt;IN - $0.05&lt;br&gt;&lt;/span&gt;]]></restrictions>
			<tc>
			</tc>
			<categories>Downloads</categories>
			<mobile_tags>
			</mobile_tags>
			<countries> AU, AT, BR, CA, DK, FR, DE, IN, IT, MX, NL, PT, SE, GB, US</countries>
			<media_types>Display, Pops</media_types>
			<languages>
			</languages>
			<tracking_duration>45</tracking_duration>
			<deep_links>0</deep_links>
			<date_created>2014-11-23 10:45:07</date_created>
			<date_updated>2015-02-15 06:19:52</date_updated>
		</program>
		<program>
			<id>148673</id>
			<name>GameOfWar-International-Android-Non Incent</name>
			<url>https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.machinezone.gow</url>
			<association_status>Approved</association_status>
			<logo>http://network.adsmarket.com/site/StoredImage?cid=3fade439</logo>
			<description><![CDATA[&lt;b style="margin: 0px; padding: 0px; text-rendering: optimizelegibility; color: rgb(102, 102, 102); background-color: rgb(255, 255, 255);"&gt;target only Android4.4+&lt;/b&gt;&lt;b style="margin: 0px; padding: 0px; text-rendering: optimizelegibility; color: rgb(102, 102, 102); background-color: rgb(255, 255, 255);"&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/b&gt;Offer Review:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;Join the ULTIMATE battle for domination of the Kingdom in Game of War &ndash; Fire Age! PLAY FOR FREE in the most addicting, interactive Action Strategy MMO GAME!&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Affiliate Benefits:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;Higher rates available for high-performing affiliates, at the advertiser's discretion.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;User Flow:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;1. User clicks on banner and is redirected to the iTunes/Google Play store&lt;br&gt;2. User successfully downloads and installs the application&lt;br&gt;3. User opens the application for the first time - pixel fires&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Typical Demographics:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;ALL]]></description>
			<restrictions><![CDATA[&lt;b&gt;target only Android4.4+&amp;nbsp;&lt;/b&gt;Please note- in order to run this offer publishers should run campaign 1177973 and leads will be redirected to the relavant campaign according to the geo. Below are the rates per geo:&lt;p class="MsoListParagraph" style="margin-top:0cm;margin-right:0cm;margin-bottom:
0cm;margin-left:36.0pt;margin-bottom:.0001pt;text-align:justify;direction:ltr;
unicode-bidi:embed"&gt;DE- $3.07&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class="MsoListParagraph" style="margin-top:0cm;margin-right:0cm;margin-bottom:
0cm;margin-left:36.0pt;margin-bottom:.0001pt;text-align:justify;direction:ltr;
unicode-bidi:embed"&gt;SG-$3.07&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class="MsoListParagraph" style="margin-top:0cm;margin-right:0cm;margin-bottom:
0cm;margin-left:36.0pt;margin-bottom:.0001pt;text-align:justify;direction:ltr;
unicode-bidi:embed"&gt;NZ-$3.07&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class="MsoListParagraph" style="margin-top:0cm;margin-right:0cm;margin-bottom:
0cm;margin-left:36.0pt;margin-bottom:.0001pt;text-align:justify;direction:ltr;
unicode-bidi:embed"&gt;RU-$2.30&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class="MsoListParagraph" style="margin-top:0cm;margin-right:0cm;margin-bottom:
0cm;margin-left:36.0pt;margin-bottom:.0001pt;text-align:justify;direction:ltr;
unicode-bidi:embed"&gt;HK- $2.30&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class="MsoListParagraph" style="margin-top:0cm;margin-right:0cm;margin-bottom:
0cm;margin-left:36.0pt;margin-bottom:.0001pt;text-align:justify;direction:ltr;
unicode-bidi:embed"&gt;IE-$3.84&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class="MsoListParagraph" style="margin-top:0cm;margin-right:0cm;margin-bottom:
0cm;margin-left:36.0pt;margin-bottom:.0001pt;text-align:justify;direction:ltr;
unicode-bidi:embed"&gt;DK- $3.84&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class="MsoListParagraph" style="margin-top:0cm;margin-right:0cm;margin-bottom:
0cm;margin-left:36.0pt;margin-bottom:.0001pt;text-align:justify;direction:ltr;
unicode-bidi:embed"&gt;CH-$3.84&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class="MsoListParagraph" style="margin-top:0cm;margin-right:0cm;margin-bottom:
0cm;margin-left:36.0pt;margin-bottom:.0001pt;text-align:justify;direction:ltr;
unicode-bidi:embed"&gt;NO-$3.84&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="MsoListParagraph" style="margin-top:0cm;margin-right:0cm;margin-bottom:
0cm;margin-left:36.0pt;margin-bottom:.0001pt;text-align:justify;direction:ltr;
unicode-bidi:embed"&gt;US- $1.92&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="MsoListParagraph" style="margin-top:0cm;margin-right:0cm;margin-bottom:
0cm;margin-left:36.0pt;margin-bottom:.0001pt;text-align:justify;direction:ltr;
unicode-bidi:embed"&gt;CA- $1.92&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="MsoListParagraph" style="margin-top:0cm;margin-right:0cm;margin-bottom:
0cm;margin-left:36.0pt;margin-bottom:.0001pt;text-align:justify;direction:ltr;
unicode-bidi:embed"&gt;JP- $1.54&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="MsoListParagraph" style="margin-top:0cm;margin-right:0cm;margin-bottom:
0cm;margin-left:36.0pt;margin-bottom:.0001pt;text-align:justify;direction:ltr;
unicode-bidi:embed"&gt;





&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="MsoListParagraph" style="margin-top:0cm;margin-right:0cm;margin-bottom:
0cm;margin-left:36.0pt;margin-bottom:.0001pt;text-align:justify;direction:ltr;
unicode-bidi:embed"&gt;AU-$3.07&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgb(102, 102, 102); background-color: rgb(255, 255, 255);"&gt;this program is under budget - daily budget is 100 leads per pub (for all geo). please contact your AM for more budget.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;Please note: This program is subject to the Google Play Developer Program Policies, which can be accessed at&lt;br&gt;https://play.google.com/about/developer-content-policy.html]]></restrictions>
			<tc>
			</tc>
			<categories>Mobile Apps,Games</categories>
			<mobile_tags>Android</mobile_tags>
			<countries> AU, CA, DK, DE, HK, IE, JP, NZ, NO, RU, SG, CH, US</countries>
			<media_types>Display, GDN, In App, Mobile Display, Pops</media_types>
			<languages>
			</languages>
			<tracking_duration>45</tracking_duration>
			<deep_links>0</deep_links>
			<date_created>2014-12-01 01:49:14</date_created>
			<date_updated>2015-02-23 08:32:43</date_updated>
		</program>
		<program>
			<id>148943</id>
			<name>JavaLP- intl' -Non Incent-MAC</name>
			<url><![CDATA[http://macmtmy.com/mac/m3?dp=1&amp;cid=[CLICKIDN]]]></url>
			<association_status>Approved</association_status>
			<logo>http://network.adsmarket.com/site/StoredImage?cid=3fc8aa2b</logo>
			<description><![CDATA[Offer Review:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;A download offer for US/CA/UK/DE/FR/AU with Media Player HD installation.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Affiliate Benefits:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;Higher rates available for high-performing affiliates, at the advertiser's discretion.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;User Flow:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;User arrives on landing page, clicks to download then runs and installs product. Conversion will fire once&amp;nbsp;a user downloads and successfully installs products onto his computer.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Typical Demographics:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;ALL&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;]]></description>
			<restrictions><![CDATA[Operating System: Mac&lt;span style="color: rgb(102, 102, 102); background-color: rgb(255, 255, 255);"&gt;Manual approval by the affiliate manager is required.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;Publisher Payouts:&lt;br&gt;US - $1.38&lt;br&gt;CA - $0.65&lt;br&gt;GB - $0.69&lt;br&gt;DE - $0.54&lt;br&gt;FR - $0.62&lt;br&gt;AU - $0.84&lt;br&gt;IT - $0.62&lt;br&gt;AT - $0.46&lt;br&gt;DK - $0.23&lt;br&gt;NL - $0.38&lt;br&gt;PT - $0.23&lt;br&gt;SE - $0.38&lt;br&gt;BR - $0.19&lt;br&gt;MX - $0.17&lt;br&gt;IN - $0.05]]></restrictions>
			<tc>
			</tc>
			<categories>Downloads</categories>
			<mobile_tags>
			</mobile_tags>
			<countries> AU, AT, BR, CA, DK, FR, DE, IN, IT, MX, NL, PT, SE, GB, US</countries>
			<media_types>Display, Pops</media_types>
			<languages>
			</languages>
			<tracking_duration>45</tracking_duration>
			<deep_links>0</deep_links>
			<date_created>2014-12-03 08:46:36</date_created>
			<date_updated>2015-02-15 06:20:06</date_updated>
		</program>
		<program>
			<id>150773</id>
			<name>CA Download WEB USA</name>
			<url>www.warrior.com</url>
			<association_status>Approved</association_status>
			<logo>http://network.adsmarket.com/site/StoredImage?cid=4096bcc7</logo>
			<description><![CDATA[Program Description&lt;br&gt;best performing download campaign for USA.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Please follow the following restrictions:&lt;br&gt;- Single Banners with the word Download (&ldquo;Descarga ahora&rdquo; or similar) are prohibited.&lt;br&gt;- Banners replicating or resembling the Portal One Landing Page are prohibited.&lt;br&gt;- Banners advertising access to movies are prohibited.&lt;br&gt;-
 Content within Banners must also be shown within the content portal. 
Anything else represented that is not in the content portal is 
prohibited.]]></description>
			<restrictions><![CDATA[&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color:#1F497D;"&gt;Download for Windows, desktop
traffic, US Firefox and Internet Explorer only&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;]]></restrictions>
			<tc>
			</tc>
			<categories>Downloads,Other</categories>
			<mobile_tags>
			</mobile_tags>
			<countries> US</countries>
			<media_types>Display</media_types>
			<languages> eng</languages>
			<tracking_duration>45</tracking_duration>
			<deep_links>0</deep_links>
			<date_created>2014-12-18 18:45:38</date_created>
			<date_updated>2015-02-19 17:01:52</date_updated>
		</program>
		<program>
			<id>151113</id>
			<name>Browser Detect- intl' -Non Incent-MAC</name>
			<url><![CDATA[http://macmtmy.com/mac/m1?dp=1&amp;cid=[CLICKIDN]]]></url>
			<association_status>Approved</association_status>
			<logo>http://network.adsmarket.com/site/StoredImage?cid=40c01d3d</logo>
			<description><![CDATA[Offer Review:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;A download offer for US/CA/UK/DE/FR/AU with Browser Detect.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Affiliate Benefits:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;Higher rates available for high-performing affiliates, at the advertiser's discretion.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;User Flow:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;User arrives on landing page, clicks to download then runs and installs product. Conversion will fire once&amp;nbsp;a user downloads and successfully installs products onto his computer.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Typical Demographics:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;ALL&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;]]></description>
			<restrictions><![CDATA[Operating System: MacManual approval by the affiliate manager is required.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Publisher Payouts:&lt;br&gt;US - $1.38&lt;br&gt;CA - $0.65&lt;br&gt;GB - $0.69&lt;br&gt;DE - $0.54&lt;br&gt;FR - $0.62&lt;br&gt;AU - $0.84&lt;br&gt;IT - $0.62&lt;br&gt;AT - $0.46&lt;br&gt;DK - $0.23&lt;br&gt;NL - $0.38&lt;br&gt;PT - $0.23&lt;br&gt;SE - $0.38&lt;br&gt;BR - $0.19&lt;br&gt;MX - $0.17&lt;br&gt;IN - $0.05]]></restrictions>
			<tc>
			</tc>
			<categories>Downloads</categories>
			<mobile_tags>
			</mobile_tags>
			<countries> AU, AT, BR, CA, DK, FR, DE, IN, IT, MX, NL, PT, SE, GB, US</countries>
			<media_types>Display, Pops</media_types>
			<languages>
			</languages>
			<tracking_duration>45</tracking_duration>
			<deep_links>0</deep_links>
			<date_created>2014-12-24 05:13:56</date_created>
			<date_updated>2015-02-15 06:20:24</date_updated>
		</program>
		<program>
			<id>151133</id>
			<name>The Buzz US - Pixel - Default</name>
			<url>www.matomy.com</url>
			<association_status>Approved</association_status>
			<description>jhkhjkhgkghkgk8</description>
			<restrictions><![CDATA[&lt;br&gt;]]></restrictions>
			<tc>
			</tc>
			<categories>Entertainment</categories>
			<mobile_tags>
			</mobile_tags>
			<countries> US</countries>
			<media_types>Display</media_types>
			<languages>
			</languages>
			<tracking_duration>45</tracking_duration>
			<deep_links>0</deep_links>
			<date_created>2014-12-24 09:34:17</date_created>
			<date_updated>2015-01-19 03:55:34</date_updated>
		</program>
		<program>
			<id>151253</id>
			<name>AntiAging-US-Non Incent-OLFA</name>
			<url>www.trylavishskin.com</url>
			<association_status>Approved</association_status>
			<logo>http://network.adsmarket.com/site/StoredImage?cid=40cde80f</logo>
			<description><![CDATA[Offer Review:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;Instead of throwing away precious dollars on expensive anti-aging skin creams that make big promises and don&rsquo;t work, one reader has discovered a skin combo that erases years off her face for only a few dollars&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Affiliate Benefits:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;Higher rates available for high-performing affiliates, at the advertiser's discretion.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;User Flow:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;On the order page, user must enter the following valid details: Name, Last Name, Address, Zip, City,&lt;br&gt;State, Phone, Email. and proceed to sale page. On the sale page the user needs to choose one of the products, enter his&lt;br&gt;valid payment details and click " Rush my order," at which point the conversion will occur.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Typical Demographics:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;ALL]]></description>
			<restrictions>Restrictions: No adult traffic.</restrictions>
			<tc>
			</tc>
			<categories>Health and Wellness,Mobile Optimized</categories>
			<mobile_tags>
			</mobile_tags>
			<countries> US, UM</countries>
			<media_types>Display, Email, Mobile Display, Pops, Search, Social</media_types>
			<languages>
			</languages>
			<tracking_duration>45</tracking_duration>
			<deep_links>0</deep_links>
			<date_created>2014-12-29 07:19:01</date_created>
			<date_updated>2014-12-29 07:20:01</date_updated>
		</program>
	</programs>
</reply>
